蓝色激情 / 碧海娇娃
我想要成为世界上最棒的冲浪者
I'm gonna be
the best surfer in the world.
我才会是世界上最棒的冲浪者呢
I'm gonna be
the best surfer in the world, not you.
她从那边出场了
看那海浪
She's just sliding in there.
Look at that wave.
安妮玛丽 查德威克
乘着今天最棒的海浪
Anne Marie Chadwick
getting the best wave of the day.
安妮玛丽，我走了
Anne Marie, I’m leaving you!
我是“好热的”浪头骇客
今天是二月三日 星期三
Hey, Howzit, wave riders?
It's hump day. Wednesday, February 3rd.
平均浪高14尺
Waves are averaging 14 feet in 18 seconds,
海面上一定有好东西 让我们出发吧
so there's definitely some size out there
in the water, and it's moving our way.
现在外面有点令人发晨呕
There's a little bit of morning sickness
out right now,
但风速提高后应该就会清爽了--
but it should clean up as the winds pick up.
风平浪静
It's flat.
是啊 我正看着
Yeah, right.
I’m looking at it.
安妮玛丽？
怎么了，杰杰？
-Anne Marie?
-What's up, JJ?
告诉伊登 她是大热门
Tell Eden she's a hottie. Hook me up.
你自己告诉她吧
潮汐看来如何？
Tell her yourself. How's Pipe looking?
哇！大浪突然起来了
至少有两个人高
Whoa! It's going off!
It's at least double overhead.
你最好过来
You better get down here.
哦 谢谢，杰杰
Okay. Thanks, JJ.
潘 起来 快起来 潘妮 快起来
唔
-Pen. Pen, come on. Get up. Penny. Get up.
-Mmm.
两个人高的大浪
It's double overhead.
他会爱你吗
& could you be loved &
会爱你吗
莉娜 嘿，莉娜 什么
&And be loved &
-Lena. Hey, Lena. -What?
两个人高的大浪
-什么？
-It's double overhead.
-What?
他会爱你吗
& could you be loved &
会爱你吗
& And be loved &
进行的如何？
How's it coming?
我无法将这铁条弄直 因为太细了
I can't get the rails right.
They're too pinched.
想要下水吗？
下水前我通常先用用望远镜望望
-You want to get wet?
-I gotta glass before work.
现在海浪正棒呢
It's perfect Pipe.
真的吗？
真的
-For real?
-For real.
走吧
好， 走吧
Let's go!
Okay, I'm coming. I'm coming.
走吧 出发罗
走咯
Get a move on. Let's go.
Let's go!
哦，可以了 走吧
Okay, got my noodles. Let's go.
快加速
Turn it up.
他会爱你吗
& could you be loved &
会爱你吗
喔！
& And be loved &
Whoo-hoo!
浪来了！
It's going off!
他会爱你吗
& could you be loved &
会爱你吗
& And be loved &
怎么了，兄弟？
What's up, bro?
太棒了 大老鼠来了
Great. The Rat Pack's here.
呕
看，凯豪和布雷登来了
It's gonna be sick.
Look, Kehau and Braden are going.
嘿，怎样，家伙们？
You know it's gonna be sick.
嘿，小子，这是怎么？
嘿，艾可，如何？
-Hey. What's up, guys?
-Hey, Rico, what's up?
嘿，女孩们
Hey, girls.
还好吗？怎么才来呀？兄弟们
What's up? How you living, man?
我们该早一个小时来的
We should have been here
at least an hour ago.
若你们早点起来就好了
我们还好啊
If you guys had gotten moving,
maybe we would've been.
怎样， 塔马约？
嘿，女孩们 如何？
-What's up, Tamayo?
-Hey. How's it, girls?
海面上如何？
How is it out there?
喔，我靠 冲浪板都打坏了
Oh, It's pretty nuts. Broke my board.
海面上狂风巨浪的
你们真的有考虑清楚？
It's pretty heavy out there.
Your girl got her head on straight this time?
有吗？
你也知道的
-Does she?
-You know it.
噢，看看谁来了
你们来做什么？
-Oh, look who's here.
-Hey, what are you girls doing here?
当然是冲浪
Same thing you are. We came to surf Pipe.
你们何不泡泡妞就算了？
Why don't you check out girlie bowls
or something?
那你何不回到你的洞里去？
Why don't you crawl back
into the cave you came from?
那我何不敲昏你们的头，
Why don't I knock you over the head
拖你们跟我一起下水？唔？
and drag you in there with me, huh?
正想试试
我最喜欢外强内柔的女孩了
-You just try that.
-I like girls that are rough and soft inside.
女孩 嫁给我吧
I'm gonna bury you, girl.
放了她 说真的 放开她
我们要走了
Let her go. Seriously, let her go.
We're out of here.
听说你要参加冲浪名人赛？
So, what's this I hear
about you surfing the Pipe Masters?
那是冲浪比赛
It's a surfing contest,
不是溺水比赛
not a drowning contest.
嘿，别再骚扰她了
她会成功的
Hey, why don't you stop hassling my girl?
She's gonna dominate.
我正等着瞧啊
我不介意能掌握海浪的女孩
Let's see it.
I don't mind girls that can charge Pipe.
小女孩认为她能掌握海浪
真是酷啊 她真的行吗？
Chick thinks she can charge Pipe. That's
cool. You think she can surf it for real?
你真的以为你行吗？
What, you think you can surf it for real?
德鲁 从现在起，什么我都能做，唔？
Well, I dated you, Drew.
I guess I can do anything, huh?
等着瞧 我去跟我的男伴们会合了
你们要的浪 我们都会将之阻断
Let's see it. I'll get my boys out there.
We'll block every single wave you want.
不论浪多大都一样 让我们走着瞧吧
No matter how big it is, we want you on it.
Let's see what's gonna happen.
来啊
Let's do it.
别光说不练 做来瞧瞧
Don't talk bubbles to me. Let's see it.
7:45 在浴室会合？
哦！
-So, meet us at the shower at 7:45?
-Okay.
尽量别滑出去太远
哦
-And stay on the inside.
-Okay.
小心点 潘
好啦
-Be careful, Pen.
-All right.
喔 看起来好像连礁石都要碎了
Looks like the reef's breaking down.
喔，他被浪打倒了
Ooh, he got shut down.
喔！
浪头真猛 真可怕
-Ooh!
-It's heavy out there.
浪太大了
It's fierce.
喔！喔，他撞到礁石了
He hit the reef.
会受伤的
That's gotta hurt.
我们还是从沙洲这边开始好了
I think we should start at the sandbar
and work our way over.
我同意
I won't argue with that.
酷夏好难受
& Now we all know summertime is a bummer with no duckets &
生活多奔波
& Honeys want money Exposed like their tummy is &
忙里来偷闲
& The one time you can just sit right there &
日子总要过
& No way you can't feel it &
世人需振作
& They're coming up skimpy with the coverup &
笑语加欢歌
& I got a long joint for ya MBug cover song &
天热阳光好
& Do what summer does and Shine &
景美天亦高
& Bright like the view of the sky inside the pipeline &
酷夏烦恼多
& It's a cruel, cruel summer, It's a cruel &
快快离开我
& Leaving me here on my own &
酷夏烦恼多
& It's a cruel, cruel summer, It's a cruel &
呼
Whoo!
现在消失了
& Now you've gone &
沙滩捡到宝
& So we're walking across the beach Bumpin'MBug tunes &
简直乐坏她
& when we spot three lovely jewels, sweet ladies having a bad day &
呼
Whoo!
当着我的面
拼命将我夸
& They looked at me with sad faces &
& Every day they'd say to me &
路面似烤炉
& Hot summer streets and the pavements are burning &
热浪围着我
& I sit around &
夏天有欢乐
烦恼也多多
& I said you got to be kidding baby &
& summer is the joint whatcha thinking &
我想笑一笑 空气似火烧
& Trying to smile, but the air is so heavy and dry &
我想骂一骂 力气也没有
& I don't give a f-Need a new rush &
来点新创意
& Let me get a hold and slap back with the new stuff &
我们来K歌
& Strange voices are saying Strange voices &
随便怎么唱 不论唱什么
& what did they say Things I can't understand what did I say &
唱到坏运消
& Tough luck It's too close for comfort &
唱到热浪走
& This heat has got right out of hand &
一起冲浪吧 日子更好过
& So the Bleste grabbed 'em dragged 'em to the sea splashed 'em in &
酷夏烦恼多
& And that's it &  & It's a cruel, cruel summer &
呼
Whoo!
现在消失了
& Now you've gone &
我想要有艘船能环岛
I want to get a boat so we can, like,
go around the island
找到一些秘密点
and get some killer secret spots.
保证一定有很多
喔，天啊 我知道
-Guaranteed, there's so many.
-God, I know. I know.
嘿！
你们躲在沙洲这干嘛？
Hey!
What's this horseshit on-the-sandbar crap?
在沙洲这里冲浪 是不可能赢得名人赛的
You're not gonna win the Masters
surfing the sandbar.
在海边时还夸口说
“德鲁 从现在起，我什么都能做”
Talking all this crap on the beach, like,
"I dated you, Drew. I can do anything."
这哪算是浪啊  真的浪在那里
This isn't Pipe. Pipe's over there.
走吧 真的浪在那里
男孩们会在前面替你们挡的
Let's go! Pipe's over there.
The boys are gonna block for you.
走吧 好啊 快
Let's do this. Let's go. Come on.
呜！ 剑
Whoo! Yeah!
兄弟们 走吧
Let's go, man.
坐而言不如起而行
Actions speak louder than words.
这景象好熟悉
什么，我的一部分要离开了？
-Now, that's the view I remember.
-What, the one of me leaving?
这也是我的最爱
It's my favorite, too.
来啊 就这个浪
Come on. Pick it up.
喜欢吗？下个浪就是你的
Like that wave, huh? Next one's yours.
欢迎来到阿瑞娜，女孩
让你试试真正的大浪
Welcome to the arena, girl.
Let's get you into something big.
安妮玛丽 你去哪儿了？
What's up, Anne Marie?
Where you been?
我以为你在我们之后
I thought you were right behind us.
今天是你的大日子 来吧
Today's your big day. Let's do it.
嗨，大伙们 她是安妮玛丽
她要跟男孩们
Right. Hey, everybody. This is my girl,
Anne Marie. She's with the boys.
一起冲浪
She's gonna get some waves out here.
只要你挡到她 就等着瞧
Any of you get in her way,
you're gonna have to deal with me.
走吧 快用力划！
Come on. Let's go.
Here it comes. Come on.
快用力划！！
Paddle, paddle!
快！用力划！！
Hurry up. Come on!
小心！ 小心！春天女郎的浪！
Watch out, watch out! Spring girl's wave.
快！ 快用力划！！
Go, Anne Marie! Paddle in!
快！ 快用力划！
快用力划！ 用力划！
Come on!
Paddle! Paddle! Paddle!
怎么一回事？
What the hell was that?
-天啊！
God!
你根本没有划！
-女孩哪会冲浪
-You ain't even paddling.
-Girls can't surf Pipe.
怎么了？
What the hell was that?
她在怕什么？
What the hell is she afraid of?
这不是选美比赛
喔，若你再这样 就会被拒绝在外
This ain't a beauty pageant.
You do that again, you're barred.
来吧， 安妮玛丽
这次你得好好干 不是胡言乱语的
Come on, Anne Marie.
You gotta do it this time. No fooling around.
好好干吧
Let's do it.
这个浪就是你的 别搞砸了
否则我不帮你了
This one's yours, right here. Don't blow it,
or I ain't gonna help you anymore.
快 快用力划，用力划！
这个浪是你的  快！ 快！
Come on. Paddle, paddle!
This one's yours now. Go! Go!
喔！
Ooh!
你的位置恰恰好
就是在那里
You were in the perfect spot.
You were right where you needed to be.
又怎样 巨浪就像猛兽般
Whatever. That thing was a beast.
还是半途退出了
浪有多大？
-Just dropped out of nowhere.
-How big was it?
真是猛
我想有三个人高
It was solid.
It was, like, triple overhead.
她感受到了
哇
She had that.
Wow.
她完全感受到了
She totally had it.
只差再多用力划而已
Yeah, she just needed
to paddle a little harder.
我不知道
I don't know.
全都在你脑子里
It's all in your
head. It's all up here.
我告诉你
若是你没犯错，
I'm telling you,
if you just would have committed,
应该可以成功的冲上去
you could have made that wave.
不管怎样  至少她试过了
那个浪如此大
Whatever. At least she went.
That wave was huge.
我就不敢去
I wouldn't have gone.
她的位置真好
She was perfectly positioned
on the wave.
为什么太阳从东方升起？
如果她有本事-
Why does the sun rise in the east?
If she had the balls to really charge it...
什么？
为什么太阳从东方升起？
-What?
-Hey, why does the sun rise in the east?
因为它从西方落下
因为地球自转的关系
-'Cause it sets in the west.
-Because that's the way the Earth rotates.
记得超人里面有一集
You remember that Supeman episode
超人将地球倒转
where he was, like,
spinning around the Earth backwards,
将地球往反方向转？
trying to rotate it in the other direction?
是啊 是啊
然后将时间回转到过去？
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
-To bring back time?
潘妮，我以为你作业完成了
Penny, I thought you finished
your homework.
没错 只是在确认一下
I did. I'm just checking it.
看起来没完
It doesn't look like
you're finished.
吉芝 别再烦她了
Geez, stop picking on her, dude.
她快要完成了
She's getting it done now.
我们才在往学校的路上
Yeah,
we're on our way to school.
我完成了
No, I finished it.
她昨晚就完成了
She should've
had it done by last night.
只是在确认一下
I'm checking it.
她只是在确认一下
昨晚就完成了 只是在确认一下
She's just checking it.
I did it last night. I'm checking it.
潘妮！ 潘妮！
什么事？
-Penny! Penny!
-What?
脚蹼
Slippers.
别偷懒逃避
No ditching.
噢
Okay.
失败了要怪你
好啦
-It sucks to be you!
-Yeah, it does.
亲爱的 总有人要上大学去
但不是我
Someone's gotta go to college, honey.
Not me.
喔，不！阿久井老师来了
Shit. It's Mr. Pukui.
记得他裤子上总是有尿痕？
Remember how he used to have pee stains
all the time?
看来他已经知道小便完如何摇了
Looks like he learned
how to shake right.
嗨，阿久井老师
安妮玛丽
-Hi, Mr. Pukui.
-Anne Marie,
这已经是你妹妹这个月第八次迟到了
this is the eighth time
your sister's been tardy in the last month.
我知道  塞车-
若你认为冲浪
-I know, traffic...
-If you think surfing
比上学更重要
我们得要做其他的安排了
is more important than school,
we gotta make other arrangements.
你知道吗，阿久井老师
You know what, Mr. Pukui?
我能想到的安排就是我母亲
The only other arrangement
I can think of right now is my mother,
然而她正好在拉斯维加斯
跟她最近一任饭票在一起
and she just so happens to be
with her latest meal ticket in Vegas,
而他又嫌我们这些拖油瓶  你懂吗？
who apparently isn't so cool
with the kid's menu, you know what I mean?
所以，这是我现在能做的
So, right now,
this is the best arrangement I can do.
你知道，潘妮是个聪明的女孩
没错
-You know, Penny's a smart girl.
-Yeah, she is.
就像他姊姊过去一样
现在 用现在式
-Just like her sister was.
-Is. Present tense.
我在这读书时学到了许多
I learned that much while I was here.
女孩们 最好注意一点
You'd better watch it, girl.
我正尽力去做
我也只能这样说了
You know, I'm doing the best I can do.
That's all I can say.
你可以做得更好
You can do better.
天啊！
God!
他非常适合穿那夏威夷衬衫
He's so ripping in that aloha shirt anyway.
我觉得他很辣
I thought he was hot.
你七年级时曾是高峰期
莉娜 闭嘴
-You did kind of peak in seventh grade.
-Shut up, Lena.
她是说性的高峰期
对了
-Sexually, she means.
-All right.
这像是什么，困住了安妮玛丽？
What is this, like, bag on Anne Marie?
呜！
Whoo!
17.53 元
夏威夷币吗？
-$1 7.53.
-That's kamaaina price?
是美金 喔
No kamaaina for candy.
莉拉尼，只是早餐而已
是啊
-Aw! Come on, Leilani. It's breakfast.
-Yeah.
早餐？抱歉 女孩们 $17.53元
里面有玉米糖浆
-Breakfast? Right. Sorry, girls. $17.53.
-This has corn syrup in it.
那是蔬菜
很营养
-It's a vegetable.
-It's nutritional.
不，我不这样认为
它含有糖份  能转化成脂肪
No, I don't think so.
It has sugar. Turns into fat,
然后胖得像我一样 喔？
and fat comes out like me, okay?
这样，$17.53元
好吧  我有五元
-So, $17.53.
-All right. I've got $5.
我有一些
你呢？
-I got some on me.
-How much do you have?
我有些现金
慢着， 我好像有-
-Yeah, I got some cash.
-Hold on, I got like...
这是什么？
我不知道， 好像是70.60分--
-What is this?
-I don't know, like, 70, 60...
真可悲 什么东西？
That's pathetic. What is that?
我没说我有很多 我有一些
I don't know. I didn't say I had a
lot of cash. I just said I had some.
我昨天给你的五元呢？
What happened
to the five bucks I gave you yesterday?
我帮萨米买食物
它又不是我们的狗，莉娜
-I bought food for Sammi.
-It's not even our dog, Lena.
狗儿要吃东西
我也是 我好饿
-Dog's gotta eat.
-Well, so do I. I'm hungry.
把剩下的小餐包吃了
我不要 我要吃早餐
-Eat the rest of this Twinkie.
-I don't want a Twinkie. I want breakfast.
小餐包就是早餐
Twinkie is breakfast.
那是 克阿拉 肯内利
她真是有名
It's Keala Kennelly. She's living the life.
一定是来参加比赛的
She must be here for the contest.
看他的冲浪板
多么精致
-Check those Jet Skis out.
-So fun.
好吧， 我们将它们加满油吧
All right, let's fill these bad boys up.
快啊 今天会很忙碌的
她跟“绿洲”的赞助商一起
-It's gonna be a busy day.
-She's with her Billabong sponsor.
快去自我介绍啊
我不
-You should go introduce yourself.
-No.
为什么不？
太奇怪了
-Why not?
-Because it's weird.
没什么好怕的 去吧
It's not weird. You can go.
快啊
不
-Yes.
-No.
嗨 能帮我们签名吗？
没问题
-Hi, can we have your autograph?
-Yeah, sure.
我帮你拿枝笔
谢谢
-I'll get you a pen.
-Thanks.
嘿，我记得这画面
栩栩如生的
-Hey, I remember this shot. It's Backdoor.
-What a life.
她接受一次杂志专访就进帐1000元
She gets a grand
every time she's in a magazine.
若是登上封面一次进帐5000元
Five grand every time she's on the cover.
你也冲浪吗？
是的
-So, you surf?
-Yeah.
她有免费的衣服，冲浪板，手表，太阳眼镜
She gets free clothes, boards,
watches, sunglasses.
根本不花一分钱
The girl doesn't have to open her wallet.
你若是在名人赛夺冠
You know,
you score one good wave at Pipe Masters,
自然有人会像赞助她一样赞助你
and you'll get sponsored just like her.
你会全世界知名
You'll get flown all around the world,
到印度 澳大利亚 大溪地去冲浪 由你决定
surf Indo, Australia, Tahiti. You name it.
周游世界，宝贝
Surf the world, baby.
有人会付钱给你在空旷完美的地方冲浪
And you'll get paid
to surf uncrowded, perfect waves.
比赛见了
喔 多谢了
-We'll see you at the contest.
-All right. Thanks. Bye.
你要做的就是引起注目
All you need to do is get noticed.
冲浪女孩
Surfer girls.
当地女孩
Local girls!
你知道你跟她一样棒
You know, you're just as good as her.
我们得上工去了，伙伴们
否则又要迟到了
We gotta go to work, guys.
We're gonna be late again.
她想当明星
& It's a jam for the ladies and a superstar &
跑来撞大运
& I could lead the whole set but never go too far &
她想当明星
& It's a jam for the ladies and a superstar &
跑来撞大运
& I could lead the whole set but never go too far &
她想当明星
& It's a jam for the ladies and a superstar &
跑来撞大运
& I could lead the whole set but never go too far &
如果命中有
& Take you from wherever to wherever you are &
肯定会发达
& Get your thing &  Get it on &
女孩们 你们迟到了
知道了 抱歉
-Girls, you're late.
-I know. Sorry.
肯定会发达
& Get your thing Get it on, superstar &
& 喔，不 &
Oh, no.
抱歉
Sorry.
明星啊
& Superstar &
肯定会发达，明星啊
&  Get your thing Get it on, superstar &
再提醒一次，今天参加全明星的客人将会抵达
As a reminder,
our Pro Bowl guests are arriving today.
它们是贵宾中的贵宾
应有最高级的服务
They are VIP return guests,
and deserve the highest level of service.
你们必须了解 没有客人
就无法在此行业中生存
We must remember, we depend on our guests
for the survival of our business.
她想当明星
& It's a jam for the ladies and a superstar &
跑来撞大运
& I could lead the whole set but never go too far &
她想当明星
& It's a jam for the ladies and a superstar &
跑来撞大运
& I could lead the whole set but never go too far &
她想当明星
& It's a jam for the ladies and a superstar &
跑来撞大运
& I could lead the whole set but never go too far &
如果命中有
& Take you from wherever to wherever you are &
呃
Ew!
如果命中有
& Take you from wherever to wherever you are &
就别放弃啦
& I can't stand to be held back &
努力去做吧
& All the ladies all got my best &
美女明星啊
& All the ladies and a superstar &
似乎这箱要寄到维加斯 却在夏威夷落了地
Look, this one packed for Vegas
and landed in Hawaii instead.
美女明星啊
我要试穿它
& All the ladies and a superstar &
I'm putting it on.
太热啊
How hot am I!
跑来撞大运
& I could lead the whole set but never go too far &
她想当明星
& It's a jam for the ladies and a superstar &
胸部太平
I don't have any boobs.
跑来撞大运
& I could lead the whole set but never go too far &
她想当明星
& It's a jam for the ladies and a superstar &
快来看， 登出来了  登出来了
Guys, guys. It's up. It's up.
看啊，安妮玛丽 查德威克 看这照片
Look, "Anne Marie Chadwick." Picture.
“这位将持外卡参赛
她是当地女子第一个夺冠者
"Wild-card entry.
This North Shore local first gained notice
在初中全国冲浪协会比赛中
"when she dominated in the junior NSSA."
你赢了，太好了！
不啊
-You dominated. Nice!
-No.
等等 你正穿着我的睡裤
You're wearing my bathing-suit bottoms
in that.
“她曾经退出巡回赛”
-I know.
-"She dropped out of the competitive circuit
“在一次溺水意外后”
嗯
-"after a near-drowning incident..."
-Mmm.
他们总是爱提这事 唔？
已经是三年前的事了
-They love bringing that up, huh?
-That was three years ago.
已经过去了
你将转进入职业 而且你会赢得这比赛
It's over with. You're gonna go pro,
and you're gonna win this thing.
我也想要被登在网络上
I want to be on the Internet.
喔，糟了！
Oh, crap!
喔，天啊
嗨？有人吗？
-Oh, my God.
-Hello? Is somebody in there?
稍等一下-我卡住了
穿你的鞋子
-Be there in... I'm stuck!
-Put your shoes on.
帮帮我 我卡住了 帮帮我
嗨？有人吗？
-Help me. I'm stuck. Help me!
-Hello? Anyone in there?
喔！喔！
Ow, ow!
快好了！
可以开门了吗？
-One second! One second!
-Can you open this door, please?
马上为您服务
鞋子
Be right with you.
Shoes.
马上开门
不是开玩笑的
Open this door right now.
I'm not fooling around.
喔，我的鞋子
这门怎会锁住？
-My shoes.
-Why was this door locked?
抱歉 门卡住了
I'm sorry. I know. It gets stuck.
维修部门马上来
Maintenance will come up and look at it
in any second.
这里发生什么事情？
我们正要清理
-What's going on in here?
-Just cleaning up.
我们正要收拾这衣物
We're just picking up the
clothes off the floor.
地板上的衣物怎么了？
What happened to all the clothes
that was on the floor?
我们折起来放到床上
We just folded them up
and put them on the bed.
我放在地板上是要你们知道
All right. I left the clothes on the floor
so that you would know
这些衣物需要干洗
that they need to be dry-cleaned.
我们需要有干洗袋
Okay, well, that's actually why we had
the dry-cleaning bags,
这也就是原因了
for that specific purpose.
为何你们不将之放入袋里？
Well, then,
why don't you put them in the bag?
没问题
这胸罩好可爱
-No problem.
-That's a cute top.
我需要你们将我的脏衣服放入袋中
"Like, I need for you guys to put
all of my crusty clothes inside of the bag."
就像将她的乳房放入胸罩中
What about the bags in her boobs?
她的乳房跟我的头一样大
Her boobs are as big as my head.
我的头够大了
And I have one big head.
抱歉
-Excuse us, please.
-Excuse us.
别管我们
Don't mind us.
足球员
Football players.
抱歉
没关系
-Excuse us.
-It's all right.
什么？
What?
懒虫
Slobs.
快用力划！ 快用力划！！
Paddle, paddle, paddle.
看啊 她们真美
Look at that. They're beautiful.
好
那么下一次你不妨去划桨试试
All right.
Next time, you're paddling.
像是这样来个美丽幽雅的划水姿势？
How about you take a sweet, luscious run
right about now?
喔，是啊，但我不这么想
但你还是可以试试看啊
Oh, yeah, I don't think so.
You can go for it, though.
是你在受训，而不是我
You're the one in training, not me.
你闻到了吗？
Do you smell that?
啤酒都不见了
Beer's gone.
喔，妈的 潘妮？
Damn it. Penny?
潘！潘？
Pen! Pen?
潘妮？
Penny?
狗娘养的！天啊！
Freaking pain in my royal ass! God!
别来 住手
Stop it, stop!
来吧 来吧
Gotta go. I gotta go.
你去哪了，安妮玛丽？
你真是棒啊？
Where you going, Anne Marie?
You too good for us?
潘妮 潘妮，醒醒吧
醒过来 我们要回去了
Penny. Penny, get up. Get up!
We're going home. Come on.
我不跟你走
这并不是请求
-I'm not going anywhere.
-It's not a request. Get up!
走开 别管我
潘妮，醒醒吧
-Go away. Leave me alone!
-No. Get up. Penny, get up!
滚开
我是认真的
-Get out of my face.
-I'm not kidding!
停下来！
别管我！滚开！
Stop! Leave me alone! Get off me!
你这婊子！
你要干什么
-You're such a bitch!
-What are you doing?
滚开！
Get off me!
为何不让我静一静？
因为我是你唯一的亲人
-Why can't you leave me alone?
-'Cause I'm all you have, Penny!
因为我是你唯一的亲人
I'm all you have right now!
我不需要你！我不管！
I don't want you! I don't care!
是你造成母亲离开的！
你就是一直在搞砸！
You're the one who made Mom leave!
You were screwing up all the time!
你知道了？很好
You know what? Fine.
很好
Fine!
我们就这样了 音乐开大声一点
We're over this. Turn the music up.
你还好吗？
You all right?
谢谢你载我
Thanks for the ride.
我应该送她去军校的
You should just send her
to military school.
剃掉她的头发
以此为戒
You should just shave her head.
That ought to send a message.
你们真是伪君子
在她的年纪时 谁不参加舞会啊
You guys are such hypocrites.
We totally partied at her age.
我们没有啊 我们不是14岁时参加
而是12岁时
-We did not. We were not 14.
-More like 12.
那是谁的错？
你们应做我的榜样才是啊
Whose fault is that?
You guys were supposed to be my examples.
喔，什么？
拜托！
-Oh, what?
-Please!
就像我们在你大一时强迫你
Yeah, like we were the ones
who forced you during freshman year
去爬沃尔康家的排水管
并偷了他们的兰姆酒
to climb up the rain gutter
at the Volcom House and steal their rum.
喔，妈的
你不记得了？
Shit.
-You remember that?
别担心
我们后来没事 对吗？
Ah, don't worry about it.
I mean, we turned out fine, right?
家务 家务
Housekeeping. Housekeeping.
喔，糟了！
呕 臭死了 那是什么？
-Oh, shit.
-God, that reeks. What is that?
那是什么味道？
我没有- 我什么都没做
-What is that smell?
-I'm not doing this. Uh-uh.
那是什么味道？
真是令人作呕，
-What is that smell?
-Freaking nasty. That's what it is.
整个房间里都充满臭味
真是令人讨厌
-It reeks in this room.
-This really sucks, right here.
喔，老天爷
好吧 我们开始吧
-Oh, my God.
-All right. Let's just get started.
好的
喔，变态！
-All right.
-Ew! Sick!
什么？ 喔！
What?
喔， 老天爷！
喔，老天爷！那--
-Oh, my God!
-Oh, my God, that...
我不要清理那些
我们还是得工作
-I'm not cleaning that up.
-We have to do it.
我们得做完工作
我不要清理
-We have to get it done.
-I'm not cleaning that up.
我们还是得做完它
真恶心
-We gotta get it done.
It's just the way it is. -It's so sick.
无颈猪 喔！
莉娜 帮我铺床
-No-neck pigs.
-Help me make the bed, Lena.
啊
Ugh!
足球员真是邋遢
Football players are so nasty.
我不晓得从何着手
I mean,
I don't even know where to start.
他们以为什么事都可以做
They think
they can get away with anything.
真是荒谬
This is ridiculous.
真恶心
什么？
-Ugh! Sick!
-What?
安妮玛丽 拿开！真恶心！
什么？
-Get it off, Anne Marie! It's stuck!
-What?
别来！
那是什么？
-It's not coming off!
-What? What is it?
避孕套
It's a condom.
真恶心！
不 别摸它！
It's stuck!
No, don't touch it!
拿开！拿开！
拿开！
-Get it off! Get it off!
-Get it off.
戴个手套
喔，拿开！
-Put some gloves on.
-Get it off!
放轻松 我拿不到
你他妈的摇来摇去
Just relax. I can't get it
if you're frigging tossing around.
脏死了
喔 天啊！
That's nasty.
Oh, my God!
喔！
Ugh!
喔 真恶心！喔！
Oh, sick! Ugh!
你知道吗？ 就这样
You know what? That's it.
喔，婚礼与蜜月在同一地点？
Wedding and honeymoon
in the same place?
女孩们，我很热
走，我们去浮潜吧
Girls, I'm hot.
Come on. Let's go snorkeling or something.
我不要顶着这头发去浮潜
别逗了
I am not snorkeling with this hair.
Give me a break.
那面具会在脸上留下难看的压痕
I know! Those masks leave the worst marks
on your face.
就像是有上百个人吐痰在上面一样
呜
-There's, like, 100 people's spit in them.
-Ooh!
有人在215房吗？
Anybody in room 215?
215房？ 有人在215房吗？有人在215房吗？
215? You ladies in 215? Gentlemen! 215?
有人在215房吗？
Anybody in room 215?
没有？ 有人在215房吗？ 外面的水中？
什么？
-No? Anybody in room 215 out in the water?
-What?
215房？ 是你的吗？
喔
-Suite 215? Is it yours?
-Oh.
喔！ 老天啊！
Oh! God!
跳！
Jump!
我在215 房
I'm in 215.
我对天发誓那是个避孕套
我认为我赢得了什么
-I swear to God, that's a condom.
-I think I won something.
我在215号房  我会赢得什么？
嗨 我是安妮玛丽
-I'm in 215. What'd I win?
-Hi. I'm Anne Marie.
我是你房间的服务员
I'm the housekeeper of your room.
莱斯利 O-线！ O-线！
-Leslie. O-line!
-O-line!
莱斯利 你有时间吗？
当然 随您吩咐
-Do you have a sec, Leslie?
-Sure, take all the time you want.
就算唱曲也行
Sugar wugar.
第一步
Step one.
呃
Ew!
第二步
Step two.
然后第三步 懂了吗？
谢谢你们的时间
And step three. You got it?
Thanks for your time, guys.
没问题
你由女侍教养
-No problem.
-Ooh! You got schooled by the maid, homie.
我正在度假 你不必-
你很有规矩
-I'm on vacation.
-You still got schooled by the maid.
度假时不用打扫房间
But you don't have to clean your room
when you're on vacation.
你很有规矩
但是不用打扫房间！
-You got schooled by the maid.
-But you don't have to clean your room
当你在度假的时候
when you're on vacation!
我正放假吗？
I'm on vacation.
真是令人讨厌，真是恶心
It was gross! It was disgusting!
我不管他们做什么
I don't care what they did.
他们是贵宾 收费最高
They are VIP. Pay the highest rate.
他们付的钱还不够叫女侍来教导他们呢
They don't pay good money
to be scolded by a housekeeper.
下周你可以领最后一张支票
安妮玛丽，冲浪季到了
You can pick up your last check next week.
Surf's up, Anne Marie.
他们尿在地板上
窗帘上到处是呕吐物
-They peed on the floor.
-There was puke all over the curtain.
请不要停我职
我们需要这笔钱
Please don't suspend me.
We need the money.
我不是要停你职 我要解雇你
I'm not suspending you. I'm firing you.
什么？
好吧，若她被解雇 我也辞职
-What?
-Well, if she's fired, I quit.
我也是
好吧
-Me, too.
-Fine.
你真的要炒我们鱿鱼？
不，我是解雇你
-You're seriously gonna fire all of us?
-No, I'm firing you.
他们是辞职 所以别想成集中解聘
They quit. So don't get any ideas
about collecting unemployment.
你们别辞职
我们需要租金
You guys, don't quit.
We need to make rent.
你应该可以留在下面更久
You could've stayed down longer than that.
伊登 憋气好难受啊
I'm tired of holding my breath, Eden.
天啊，
她就是爱惹我生气
God,
she just loves pissing me off.
你看她 她不是来冲浪的
她只是来吸引众人目光的
Look at her. She's not even out here to get
waves. She just wants to get attention.
那她在那些家伙之间有何搞头？
What does she see in those guys anyway?
他们简直是形容枯槁
They're such burnouts.
你也是一样
什么？
-Same thing you did.
-What?
好一个正冲及回冲浪峰
Cut body and a nice cutback.
喔， 太好了
她的姿态不佳
-She's right.
-She's got a bad attitude.
她的表现不该是这样啊
It's not who she is.
内侧！对啊！我在这！
！
Inside! Got it! I'm on it!
打败它
Beat it!
嘿，嘿，嘿！就这样！
Hey, hey, hey! Got it!
嘿！嘿，你到哪里？
Hey! Where are you going?
我在这！走开！
I'm on it! Get off!
德鲁，我做到了！
Drew, I got it!
嘿！
Hey!
我有这部分 你有何问题？
I had the section. What's your problem?
你该长大了
You need to grow up.
你弄坏了冲浪板并非是我的错
你这笨新手 你真傻
It's not my fault you broke your board,
you stupid kook.
不，你是个疯子
别再闯进来
No, you're a kook!
Don't ever drop down on me again!
没错
回家吧 打败它
Yeah, that's right.
Go home. Beat it, blondie.
猴子
Donkey.
你可否将它黏回去？
不
-Can you glue it back together?
-No.
好吧，我只是开车经过而已
喔
-I was just driving by.
-Okay.
嗯，事实上，是旅馆的人告诉我可以来找你
Well, actually, the guy at the hotel
told me where I could find you.
你知道 冲浪相当的可怕
So, that's pretty awesome,
you know. Surfing.
对
嘿，听着
-Right.
-Hey, listen,
我要为我朋友在旅馆的事道歉
I wanted to apologize
for my friend back at the hotel.
莱斯利平常可能不修边幅，但当朋友有难
You know, Leslie's kind of messy, but when
your ass is hanging out in the pocket,
他总是会挺身而出
he's the guy you want
protecting your backside.
所以当你有需要时 可以求教于他
So, next time your ass is hanging back
in the pocket, he's your guy.
我会记得的
怎么了 安妮玛丽？
-I'll remember that.
-Hey, what's up, Anne Marie?
嘿，本
你弄坏了冲浪板 真是糟透了
-Hey, Ben. How're you doing?
-You broke your board? That sucks.
我敢说你当时一定是猛冲
-Yeah.
-Bet you were charging, though.
差不多是这样
嘿，我认识你吗？
-Something like that.
-Hey, don't I know you?
我不晓得 或许吧
对了 你是那个四分卫对不对？
-I don't know, maybe.
-Yeah, you're that quarterback.
是啊 我也玩玩足球
就是啦？
-Yeah, I play some football.
-That's right, huh?
好鞋啊 兄弟
Nice shoes, bro.
谢谢
Thanks.
不晓得 嗯 你有没有收过徒弟？
Um, anyway, I was wondering
if maybe you've taught anybody.
收过徒弟？
有啊 教冲浪啊
-Taught anybody?
-Yeah, how to surf.
不
嗯 你知道 我最近都有空闲
-No.
-Well, you know, I've got some free time.
真好
听着，我一直都喜欢学习
That's nice.
-Well, I'd love to learn.
你说得倒简单
我知道 但是那看起来很有趣
-It's not easy.
-I know, but it looks really fun out there.
你会受伤
我很确定我会照顾自己
-You can get hurt.
-I'm sure I could handle myself.
这小子是里克
You know what? There's this guy Rick.
他会带你用海绵冲浪板玩些小浪
He'll set you up with a sponge board
and some baby waves.
他很温柔
你呢？
-He's gentle.
-And you are?
我不温柔
对
-Not.
-Right.
注意了
谁是智族约克？
-Check it out.
-Who's GQ jock?
呵 呵 呵
Ha ha ha
这是怎么一回事？
Hey. What was that all about?
我不知道
需要教他点什么吧
I don't know.
He wanted lessons or something.
安妮玛丽！
什么？
-Anne Marie!
-What?
学习？钱呢？我们早破产了？
Lessons? Money? We're broke?
他没提到钱
那你问了吗？
-Well, he didn't say anything about paying.
-Well, did you ask?
你们今晚动身吗？不 什么时候？
走 走 走！
-You guys are going tonight? No. What time?
-Go, go, go!
我不知道 我有点迷糊了
去找他
-I don't know. I'm kind of lost.
-Go get him, go get him!
嘿！嘿！
我会尽力而为 别挂
-Hey! Hey!
-I'll try to make it. Hang on.
什么？
多少？
-What?
-How much?
什么？
多少？
-What?
-How much?
我再打给你
喔，妈的！
-I'll have to call you back.
-Shit!
嘿！小心！看路啊！
Hey! Watch where you're going!
快点！去追他 来吧
Hurry up! Go get him. Come on.
喔，快！快！快！
Okay, hurry, hurry, hurry!
嘿 嘿，听着
多少？
For lessons. How much?
我不知道 一般是多少？
I don't know. What's the going rate?
每小时二十元
二十元？
-Twenty bucks an hour.
-$20?
太贵了吗？
十五块啦？
-Too much?
-$15?
十五块？旅馆要价150 元
好 我付
-$15? The hotel charges $150.
-I'll pay that.
喔！115 元 为了冲浪课程？
就这样了 对吗？
150 bucks! For surf lessons?
That's it, right?
不然我们是再说什么？
有其他朋友吗？
-What else are we talking about?
-Got any friends?
当然有
Sure I do.
喔！好啊！
Whoo! Yeah!
你脸上那是什么，潘？
什么脸上？
-What's with the face, Pen?
-What face?
亲爱的 别担心
只是一个下午而已
Don't worry, honey.
It's just one afternoon.
你终究会有时间怀孕
继续你幸福快乐的生活
You'll still have plenty of time
to get pregnant and go on welfare.
好主意
应该会很好玩，潘
-Good idea.
-It'll be fun, Pen.
我们来跟游客敲竹杠
不 我们不敲任何人竹杠
-We'll play rip off the tourist.
-We're not ripping anyone off.
有人付1000元就住一晚
不是自己求人敲他竹杠吗
Anyone who pays $1,000 a night
for a room is just begging to be ripped off.
我昨天看到那些家伙
走进汤米巴哈马假日酒店
I saw those guys
walk into Tommy Bahama yesterday
后面跟四个穿着丝绸内衣的女孩
and drop four Gs on silk boxers.
那怎么可能？
那是内衣
Yeah. How is that possible?
It's underwear.
他们的钱多的花不完
都是职业美式足球员 你开玩笑吧?
Yeah, those guys got money to burn.
They play in the NFL. Are you kidding?
我不在乎有没有钱
有其他更重要的
I don't care about the money.
Anything is better than this.
喔，老天啊！
是 妈的
-Oh, my God.
-Yeah, right.
快离开这里
潘妮！
-Let me out here, you guys.
-Penny.
我以为他的朋友应该是很有名
I thought his friends would be hot at least.
被人看到是跟你们在一起会很尴尬
This is so embarrassing to be seen with you.
你们要教我们冲浪吗？
You gonna teach us how to surf?
Teach us how to surf.
我要走了，宝贝
I'm ready to go, baby.
王八蛋
Bastards!
来吧 每个150 元
Hey, guys, come on. It's $150 each.
要是看到认识的人怎么办 天啊！
What if we see people we know? God.
管他的  就是冲浪课程吗
运动员都像是这样吗？
Whatever. It's surf lessons.
So this is what jocks look like?
150 元
我们去冲浪吧，大个儿
-One hundred and fifty bucks.
-Let's go surfing, big daddy.
女孩们 怎么了？
What's up, girls?
她们是莉娜跟伊登 我是安妮玛丽
This is Lena and Eden. I'm Anne Marie.
嘿 我们今天就冲浪吗？
嗨
-Surf? hi.
-Hey.
小心 我会确认你会在那溺水
If you don't watch out,
I'll make sure you drown out there.
今天还好吗？ 马特 很高兴认识你
这是我小妹，潘妮
-Hey, how's it going? Matt. Nice to meet you.
-This is my little sister, Penny.
你好 小妞？
冲浪小家伙
What's up, little mama? Little surf baby.
你要穿那样去冲浪吗？
喔 不 我会穿我的大-大-大-大去
-You're gonna surf in that?
-Hell, no. I'm gonna surf in my da-da-da-da's.
穿什么？
我的大-大-大-大 去！
-In your what?
-My da-da-da-da's!
大 大 大 大
Da-da-da-da's.
你穿的是“蛋袋”
有些人是这么叫它
-You're wearing nut huggers.
-Some might call them that.
但我叫它“蛋箱”
你要教我们冲浪了
I call them nut containers.
You're gonna teach me how to surf.
我数三
一 二 三
-On three?
-One, two, three.
站起身！
Snap up!
别撞到小弟
No duck butt.
喔 对了
Oh, yeah.
喔！该死，不！
Oh! Hell, no!
加油 快！划啊！
Come on. Go! Paddle!
加油！加油！莱斯利
Come on! Come on, Leslie.
快！
喊啊
-Go!
-Call me.
呀呼 呀呼
呼 呀
Yahoo Yahoo
Whoo! Yeah!
哇
啊
-Whoa!
-Ahh!
呜
Ooh!
好了没？
好了
-Okay. Ready?
-Okay.
开始划水！划！快划！快划水！
All right. Start paddling! Paddle! Go! Go!
好啊！站起身！站起身！站起身！
Yeah! Yes! Get up! Get up! Get up!
头部维持正中！向前倾！手张开！
加油！快！
Put your head in the center.
Lean forward. Hula hands! Come on! Go!
喔！
Whoa!
Yeah!
好了 回来这里！ 再一次！
Come on. Get back out here! One more time!
嘿，我在教你们
Hey, I'm giving a lesson.
该你了 快啊 快划水！快划水！
There you go. Come on. Paddle, paddle.
呜
Whoo!
Yeah!
真是好棒
That was so good.
太不可思议了
-That was so good.
-That was incredible.
哇
Whoa!
心灵畅快吗？
是啊 当然
-Are you psyched?
-Yeah, totally.
我们去那边玩大一点的浪
Let's go and catch one of those big ones.
那边？你确定你可以驾驭吗？
绝对可以
-Out there? Okay, sure you can handle it?
-Yeah. Definitely.
来啊，马特 对了 继续划水啊！
Come on, Matt. You got it,
you got it. Paddle, paddle, paddle.
用力啊  再用力向前划
Harder. Come on. You gotta dig.
好啦，安妮玛丽，我会跟上你的
All right, Anne Marie,
I'm right there with you.
别担心我 我专精此道
Don't worry about me. I got this mastered.
我是个职业足球员  喔，妈的！
I am a football player. Oh, shit!
喔！
Oh!
只要在多划几下 就做到了 多划几下
A couple more. You got it.
Just a couple more waves.
乌龟式保护！躲到冲浪板下面！快翻过来！
Dig! Turtle!
Get under your board! Turn it over!
别放弃 来啊 快划！
Don't give up. Come on. Paddle.
一定要穿过这浪 来了
All right, here we go.
Gotta make it over this wave. Here we go.
快划水！
快离开！
-Paddle, paddle.
-Hey, get out of the way!
用力划！就是这样
Harder. There you go.
你还好吗？
喔 真是刺激
-You okay?
-Oh, man, that was intense.
这里的浪头较高 你确定不要近岸一点？
I know. It's getting big out here.
Sure you don't want to go in?
不 我意思是 我们这里安全吗？
No. I mean, are we safe out here?
要看你怎么想罗
但是 还蛮安全啦
That depends what you think is safe,
but yeah, pretty much.
这个如何？
不 这哪算是浪啊
How about this one here?
No, this one's not a wave.
喔 就差一点
Almost.
马特，一定会有的 我保证
回来
We'll get you one, Matt. I promise.
Come on back.
是这样喔
马特 要有耐心一点 一定会有的
Oh, man.
-Just be patient, Matt. We'll get you one.
安妮玛丽，我们要走了！
Anne Marie! We're leaving!
嘿， 甜心，你何不来帮帮我？
Hey, sweetie. Why don't you come over here
and help me out a little bit?
得要我们俩才拿得动
Gonna need two of us to carry this one.
时候不早了 我们该回去了
Maybe we should go in.
It's getting late.
不 我没抓住一个浪头不走
I'm not leaving
until I catch one of these things.
这个如何？
快掉头过来 快啊 快，别搞砸了
-How about this one?
-Okay, yeah, turn around, quick. Egg beat.
就是这样，马特
快划水！ 快划水！快划水！
There you go, Matt. This is it. Paddling.
Start paddling. Go! Go! Paddle! Paddle!
站起身  站起身
Stand up. Stand up.
这就对了！
Yeah!
呜
Whoo!
哇
Whoa!
这就对了！
马特 干的好！
-Yes! Yeah!
-There you go! Good job, Matt! Whoo!
-Yeah.
干的好！
是啊！
-Good job.
-Yes.
早上好
Good evening.
嗨 欢迎来到拉纳开旅馆
Hi. Welcome to the Lanakai.
没关系 我只是顺路送他过来
No, it's all right.
I'm just dropping him off.
你何不进来喝杯饮料？
Wait. Why don't you come in for a drink?
嗯，不，好是好，可我-
我什么？
-Yeah, no, I'd love to, but I...
-But what?
我得要回去了
懂我的意思吗？
I have to get back to my side of the island.
You know what I mean?
喔 不懂 为什么？
因为我在集训当中
-Uh, no. Why?
-'Cause I'm in training.
名人 对
名人赛
-Pipe... Line.
-Pipeline.
冲浪名人赛
冲浪名人赛，对
-Master. Pipe Masters, right.
-Pipe Masters, right.
好吧， 我告诉你
Well, I tell you what.
我只有40块钱
做什么？
-Uh, I've only got 40 bucks.
-For what?
付你的钟点费啊
For you. For the lesson.
喔 对啊，但若是你跟我回房去
我会把剩下的付清
But if you want to come up to my room,
I'll give you the rest of the money.
我 我很乐意，但看到那边的家伙了没？
I would really like to do that,
but see those guys over there?
他们会看着我们往你房间去，
They see us heading up to your room,
明天以前 岛上一半的人
都会说我跟你上过床
half the island's gonna have us
sleeping together by tomorrow morning,
肯定的
真的吗？
-guaranteed.
-Really?
这就是所谓的“椰子无线电”
It's the coconut wireless. Yeah.
那真的很严重
是啊
-That's very serious.
-It's great. Yeah.
那么 你等会儿我会带钱下来
All right. Well, in that case, you wait here.
I'll come right back with your money.
嘿  等等
All right. Wait.
我上去
确定？
-I'll come up.
-You sure?
喔 我不想破坏你的名誉或什么
Okay. 'Cause I don't want
to ruin your reputation or anything.
谢谢 我很重视
Thanks. I'll worry about that.
好吧
喔
-All right.
-Okay.
这样 你走电梯 我走后边门
You go up the elevator. I'll go up
the back way, so it's, like, inconspicuous.
真是鬼鬼祟祟  就像是007电影一样
闭嘴啦
-It's so sneaky. It's like James Bond.
-Just shut up.
抱歉
Excuse me.
她在干嘛？
What the hell is she doing?
嘿
-Hey.
你要去哪？
Where you going?
我要-
我--我不知道这是不是你的房间
I just...
I didn't know if that was your room or not.
这是我房间
喔
-It's my room.
-Yeah.
请进
喔 谢谢
-Come in.
-Okay. Thanks.
哇
Wow.
晚上看起来不一样
是啊 很不错吧
-Looks different at night.
-Yeah, it's pretty nice.
我想--我想要
喔 厕所在那边
-I'm just gonna go...
-It's right there.
好的 我知道在哪  谢谢
I know where it is. Thanks.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
喔，我只是要把藏着的钱找出来
I'm just trying to find the money that I hid.
什么，怕给女侍偷走？
是啊
-What, from the maid?
-Yeah. Right.
看着
一 二三四五六七
Uh, let's see.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
八九
不 等等 那-那不，
-eight, nine...
-Wait. That's way, way...
--那不就是1，000 块钱
我在这要一周 每天 150块钱
That's $1,000. I'll be here a week.
That's $150 a day,
我一次付清 自己打折少付50块
so I gave myself a $50 discount
for paying up front.
你这是要买断我？
不 不是 我只是不想要失去你
-Are you trying to buy me?
-No. No. I just don't want to lose you.
我可以问一个怪问题吗？
Can I ask you a really weird question?
可以
你喷了我的古龙水吗？
-Yeah.
-Are you wearing my cologne?
嗯 是啊
Yes.
那，嗯 很适合你
It smells good on you.
你是否该接一下
好吧
-You should probably get that.
-Yeah. Right.
嘿 嘿，宝贝
Yeah? Hey. Hey, sweetheart.
你好一些了吗？
Are you feeling better?
是啊
我先前有打，但没人接电话
Yeah, no, I tried to call earlier,
but no one was there.
是 我想你 我也想你
Yeah, I miss you, too. I miss you, too.
忙乱了一天
马特，我要--
-It's been hectic.
-Matt, I'm gonna...
听着 我再打给你 好吗？
好啦
Listen, let me call you back, all right?
All right.
我也爱你 好吧 再见
I love you, too. All right. Bye.
对不起
Sorry.
我想这就是人家说的“无博爱”定律
I guess that's why
they have that no-fraternization rule.
你的意思是？
What do you mean?
接到妻子的电话质疑
Management gets call
from irate wife
怎么凌晨两点有一个女侍在房里
wondering why maid is in husband's room
at 2:00 in the morning.
那不是我妻子
妻子 女友 男友
-That's not my wife.
-Wife, girlfriend, boyfriend.
不 真的 那不是我妻子
看啊 是我外甥女
No, really. It's not my wife.
Look, it's my niece.
真的，我姊姊的女儿 洛贝卡
就是她
Actually, my sister's daughter, Rebecca.
There she is.
是这样啊
So.
我发誓
I swear.
她很漂亮
是啊 她长的很甜
-She's beautiful.
-Yeah, she is. She's a sweetheart.
对不起 小外甥女搞不清楚时差观念
Sorry about that. It's kind of strange
with the time difference and all.
或许我该走了 时间很晚了
I should probably go. It's getting late.
好吧  明天我们有冲浪课程吗？
All right. Do I have a surf lesson tomorrow?
当然有
好吧
-Definitely.
-All right.
喔！
Okay.
再见 再见
-Bye.
再见
Bye.
我以为你现在正要给他上课呢
I thought you were
just giving him lessons.
没错
是啊 教什么？
-I did.
Yeah, in what?
潘妮 没有做完功课
Penny didn't finish her homework.
你又没在这帮我
应该要自己做作业的
-You weren't here to help me.
-Guys, she's gotta do her homework.
别胡扯什么
因为你正在那边工作
Don't give us shit
'cause you were out there working it.
闭嘴
别否认
-Shut up.
-Don't deny it.
你就像是在做些无聊的事
You were working it
like a rib without the sauce.
好吧 发生什么事？
喔 老天 什么事都没有发生
-What happened?
-Oh, my God. Nothing.
喔 当然 告诉我们啦
Oh, sure. Tell me what happened.
不
有没有玩些什么？有没有？有没有？
-No.
-Did you get some play? Did you? Did you?
我们吻了两秒钟
没啥大不了的
We kissed for, like, two seconds.
It wasn't a big deal.
我相信是
我出多少钱你才要讲？
I'm sure you did.
How much am I supposed to buy that for?
你把我当成什么了
我不知道
-God, what do you take me for?
-I don't know.
说真的 来吧 还有呢？
这里， 够付我们的帐了
-Seriously. What else? Come on.
-Here, this will pay the bills.
这似乎有 1，000块钱
我觉得好像是你的淫媒
There's, like, $1 ,000 here.
I feel like your pimp.
你要知道如何接吻
或者其他
You must know how to kiss, huh?
Or you must know how to do something else.
潘妮 晚安 你现在就要上床去
Goodnight, Penny. You're going to bed now.
嘿
怎么了？
-Hey.
-What's up?
听着，我不想要唠叨
Look, I hate to be the buzzkill here,
但比赛剩下一周了
我认为现在不适合--
but the contest is in a week,
and I just don't think that it's time for...
我知道 但我答应他明天也有冲浪课
I know. But I did promise him
another lesson tomorrow.
可以取消吗？
不
-Can't you just blow him off?
-No.
为何不？
因为他已经付我钱了
-Why not?
-Because he already paid me.
真的
伊登
-Exactly.
-Eden.
我明天要租一个喷射滑板 （水上摩托车）
Well, I wanted
to rent a Jet Ski tomorrow.
让你适应名人赛
Put you into some size.
Get you ready for Pipe.
我们下午4:00 餐厅见
All right, well,
I'll meet you at the launch at 4:00.
何不早一点？
Why not earlier?
我尽量啦
I'll meet you there as soon as I can.
我们要去哪？
Where are we going again?
一个旅馆不会告诉游客的景点
A little spot the hotel
does not tell the tourists about.
天啊 你开车就像冲浪一样
我开车就像是我在冲浪一般
Oh, my God. You drive like you surf.
I drive like I wish I surfed.
真美
是啊 我小时候常常来
-Wow. This is beautiful.
-Yeah, I used to come here when I was a kid.
我梦见过整晚在冲浪
I've been dreaming
about surfing all night.
明尼苏达也有迷冲浪啊
哦，是啊
-Oh, Minnesota's got surf stoke, huh?
-Oh, yeah.
快
Go!
哇！冲上去
Whoa! Hop on.
小心
Watch out. Whoa.
Yeah!
明尼苏达 你有几个姊妹啊？
How many sisters you got, Minnesota?
五个
五个？
-Uh, five.
-Five?
五个
真的吗？你是唯一的男生？
-Five.
-Really? You're the only boy?
是啊
那就是了
-Uh, yep.
-That explains it, then.
就是什么？
Explains what?
因此你不怕女人的威吓
That's why you're not intimidated by women.
是啊
有那么好笑吗？
-Yeah.
-Why is that funny?
因为 我真的怕死了女人
Because I'm scared shitless of women.
我姊姊常常揍我
看着
My sisters would beat me on a regular basis.
See, look.
看到我的手指无法伸直了吗？
是的
-See how I can't extend my finger?
-Yes.
因为我八岁时被姊姊达娜打断
'Cause my sister Dana broke it
when I was eight,
只因为我不原离开她的房间而已
just because I wouldn't get out of her room.
是这样的
Because it's broken that way,
我扔出球，嗖的飞了出去，
比一般更有力量
when I throw the football,
it gives it a nice little zip.
只是轻轻的碰了一下？
是的
-A nice little touch?
-Exactly.
噢，有人来了
Uh, I think we got company.
噢，太好了
你认识这些人吗？
-Oh, great.
-What's up?
是的，我认识
我们得走了
-You know those guys?
-Yeah, I do. We gotta go.
真要走吗？
是得
-Really?
-Yeah.
收拾东西
Prepare to get vibed.
这里是“卡普”
意思是只对夏威夷本地人开放，小白
This place is kapu.
That means off-limits to you, haole.
你们好啊！
这里只对本地人开放
-What's up, guys?
-This is a local spot.
是的 我是本地的
他不是
-Yeah, and I'm a local.
-He's not.
你好！小白
德鲁，让开！
-What's up, haole boy?
-Drew, back off.
我们在这里长大，你只是来这里度假
We grew here. You flew here.
这不关他的事
我很抱歉带他来
It's not his fault.
I'm sorry for bringing him.
你在我们的海滩上干什么，小白
What are you doing on our beach, haole boy?
你不是这里人，就不能在这里冲浪
You don't live here, you don't surf here.
德鲁
我们5秒钟就从这里消失
Drew,
we'll be out in five seconds.
这里只对本地人开放
这里是我们男孩子的地方
This is a local spot.
Hey. This place is for the boys.
你知道不能让这个家伙来的
安妮玛丽 干什么呀
You know not to bring this guy over
here, Anne Marie. What's up with that?
兄弟，冷静点好吗！
Why don't you just relax, brah?
兄弟，谁跟你是兄弟了啊！
德鲁
-"Brah?" You telling me "brah"?
-Drew.
够了 你想打架吗？
德鲁 不要再碰我
-Where are you from, you honky?
-Drew, stop it.
你要干什么
德鲁 不要再碰我
-You want some of this?
-Drew, stop it.
不要再碰我
别碰她
-Don't even touch me.
-Don't touch her.
不准碰她！
德鲁 你想干嘛？
-What are you gonna do?
-Drew, grow up!
我拿了他的钱包
走吧，去冲浪了
I've got his wallet.
We're out of here. Let's go surf.
够了， ！德鲁
要像个大人
Stop, stop, stop. Drew, stop!
Act like an adult.
到车里去 够了 不要打了
走开
Just get in the car. Seriously, stop it.
Walk away.
够了 不要打了
你怎么这个样子啊？
Seriously, stop it.
Why do you have to be like this?
对了，
不准碰她
-Right, get over there.
-Don't touch her.
那你想怎么样啊？
What are you gonna do?
求你了！你干什么呀？
你要干什么
-Please! What are you doing?
-You want some of this?
德鲁
Drew!
你们两个！够了！不要打了！
走开
Both of you! Get off! That's enough! Stop!
Get off!
你上车  行了！上车！
Get in the car! Stop it!
Stop. Get in the car.
不要打了，上车  上车啊
Now, stop it. Get in the car.
Just get in the car.
滚开
Walk away.
你真是一混蛋
You're an asshole.
我就该这么做
I do what I do best.
好了，兄弟
你了不起
-Relax, bro.
-You kicked his ass.
什么
了不起
-What?
-Kicked his ass.
有钱就了不起了，笨蛋
滚回去吧
Nice meeting you guys.
-Beat it. Go back to the mainland.
真愚蠢
This is bullshit.
我租了一辆水上摩托车
伊登 我知道
-I rented a Jet Ski.
-Eden, I know.
真抱歉，真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I said I was
sorry a hundred times.
算了
真是他妈的
-Whatever.
-She's scared, man.
喂
Hello?
她怎么说？
What'd she say?
她都不在 干嘛
She's messing up, man.
没什么事吧！
噢，没有
-Everything okay?
-Oh, yeah. We'll be okay.
我明白为什么那些游客
不离开他们的酒店房间了
I can see why the tourists here
never leave their hotels.
不要谈那个
夏威夷人不都是这样的
他们-他们只是太过头了点
Oh! Don't say that. That's not real Hawaii.
They're just... They're just crazy.
他们特别在意他们的土地
他们的沙滩和那些海浪
They're so protective of their land
and their waves, especially.
还有他们的女人吧？
And their women?
怎么了？
真的很高兴来这里度假
-What?
-I'm glad I'm here.
噢！
Oh!
我要去训练了
那我起来
-I have to go to practice.
-I'll get up.
不用，不用了 继续你的好梦
真的？
-No, no, no, no. Sleep in.
-Are you sure?
当然了  继续睡吧
喔
-Yeah, you sleep.
-Okay.
那再见
再见
-Bye.
哦，糟了，
糟了
Shit. Shit.
喂
莉娜，是我
-Hello?
-Lena, it's me.
你在哪里啊？
不要担心我了
-Hey. Where are you?
-Don't worry about it.
不会吧，你在他的房间里？
你别管太多
-You're at his room, huh?
-It's none of your business.
我只想问问潘妮上学有没有问题
Listen, I just want to make sure
Penny gets to school okay.
没问题 不要担心
Yeah, yeah. Don't worry about it.
告诉我你们干了些什么啊？
以后会告诉你的了
-What happened?
-I will tell you everything.
快点告诉我，小酒虫
Come on, little hooch.
不要这样叫我嘛 哦，我的天
Shut up. Oh, my God.
好吧好吧
那再见
-All right.
-Bye.
房间服务部，有什么可以帮你的吗？
Room service. Can I help you?
我想要份早餐
Yes, I'd like to order
some breakfast, please.
当然 托尔曼太太 你想吃点什么呢？
Of course, Mrs. Tollman. What can I get you?
嗯，草莓蛋糕吧
Uh, the blueberry waffles.
打扫房间的，
Housekeeping!
早安，阿洛哈，看看我们的小公主
Well, aloha! Look at you,
little miss princess.
是，是，是
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你的漂亮拖鞋很合脚啊
我还穿着去游泳池了
-So the glass slipper fit, huh?
-I even went in the pool.
算了吧 你可真是够刺激人的啊
-Shut up! You're so irritating!
这不关我的事 是他追我的
还让我吃什么草莓蛋糕
It's wasn't my fault. He abducted me
and forced me to eat blueberry waffles.
草莓蛋糕？哪里啊？
外面桌上
-Blueberry waffles? Where?
-Outside.
很好吃的
Nice.
你干什么啊？
帮忙啊
-What are you doing?
-Helping.
你不再是个女侍了
过来 伊登 不要生我的气了
-Why? You're not a maid anymore.
-Come on, Eden. Don't be mad at me.
我没有
I'm not mad.
嗯！太好吃了  你怎么不加点奶油
Mmm. These are so good. You didn't
save me any whipped cream, though.
某人认为你穿着比基尼很性感，你就忘了比赛
Some guy thinks you look hot in a bikini,
and you forget all about the contest.
不是那样的，你知道的
That's not fair, and you know it.
香槟酒？你可真乐啊？
别说了
-Champagne? How cheesy are you?
-Shut up!
我不是生你的气
I'm not mad.
我只是刚好知道你在那里
It's just...
I happen to know that you kick ass out there,
你努力工作，去你想去的地方
and you worked very hard
to get to where you are.
我知道
I know.
冲浪名人赛三天后就开始了
每个赞助商都会来这里
Pipe is in three days.
Every single sponsor is here.
那天肯定有人会脱颖而出
不是你就是其他人
And it's just you and one
other girl out there.
我了解，我明白  好了吧
人们对你抱有很大的希望
-I know. I got it. Okay?
-People would kill to be in your shoes.
我知道
I got it!
嘿，听我说 比赛肯定是放在第一位的
没有什么能改变
Hey, listen to me.
Contest comes first. Nothing changes that.
我将脱颖而出
会胜过你
I'm gonna whip it around
and put you into this left!
Yeah!
呜
Whoo!
Yeah.
看 看 来了
This is it. This is it, right there!
太棒了
Yeah!
糟了
Shit!
安妮玛丽！
Anne Marie!
你在哪里
Where are you?
安妮玛丽！
Anne Marie!
伊登，我在这里
Eden, over here!
快点快点
我们离开这里
Get on! Get on!
Come on. We gotta get out of here.
我抓到你了！我抓到你了！握紧
I got you! I got you! Hold on.
走啊！怎么了？握紧！
Move! What's wrong? Gun it!
伊登，离开这里！
哦，糟了
-Eden, get out of here!
-Oh, shit!
往外舀水！
Bail, bail, bail!
还好吧
刚才你在哪里啊？
-You all right?
-Where were you?
我就在你后面
看来我不行了
I was right behind you.
I couldn't get in without getting crushed.
你追我太急
你想我提前就被淘汰吗
You whipped me in way too deep,
and you need to kick out earlier.
难道我们不是一步一步在训练吗？
我想参赛
-Are you done with your excuses now?
-I want to go in.
我们休息一下吧
We'll rest for a minute.
我不想休息
我差点就死在那里了
I don't want to get some rest!
I almost frigging died out there!
你死不了
你只是在水下，差不多5秒钟
You did not almost die.
You were under for, like, five seconds.
不要象个巴比娃娃
你说什么，啊？
-Stop being such a Barbie.
-What did you say to me? What?
巴比娃娃  你怎么了
A Barbie? What is your problem?
我说如果这样你都受不了的话，
Look, all I'm saying
is that if you can't handle this,
你就不可能为那场比赛做好充分的准备
there's no way you're gonna be ready
for the Pipe Masters.
那好啊，你去啊
你有胆量，伊登，你去啊
Then you go!
You're so frigging ballsy, Eden, you go!
我不能  我不在被邀请的行列里
I can't. I wasn't invited.
我不管  你到底想要我怎么样啊
我想让你做的
-I don't know what the hell you want from me.
-You know, what I want from you
就是你自己去实现你的梦想
不要通过我
is to get your own life
and stop living through me!
实现你的梦想吧
Get your own dreams!
就算是的
那你想退出吗，你想引起人们的注意吗？
So that's it?
You gonna go run off and be a pro-ho, huh?
至少，还有人关心我
At least I have someone
that's interested in me!
怎么听起来那么熟悉啊？
遇到困难就缩头
Why does this seem so familiar, huh?
Run away when things get tough.
我重复了好多遍了，
我发现我好像在哄小孩一样
"I'm stressed out.
I think I'm gonna ditch my kid
为了一个在刚认识的男人而放弃比赛吗
闭嘴，伊登 我是认真的
-"and run away with some guy I just met."
-Shut up, Eden. I'm not kidding.
听起来很熟悉
不要管我！
-Sounds a little bit too familiar.
-Leave me alone!
像是母亲又像是女儿
闭嘴
-Like mother, like daughter.
-Shut up!
你想干什么
我就想不干了
That's what you're gonna do?
You're just gonna quit?
从我面前消失
那些看不起你的家伙看来是对的
-Get out of my face, Eden.
-You gonna prove these guys right?
为什么那些混蛋不认为你能冲浪呢
就是因为你放不开
Assholes who think that you can't surf Pipe
because you don't have the balls!
是的我也这么认为， 所以我不干了
我不干了
I guess so, then, 'cause I quit. I quit!
你不是个儒夫  你只是害怕
You're not a quitter. You're just scared.
嘿
Hey.
噢，天啦  你这是怎么了？
Oh, my God. What's wrong?
发生了什么事情吗？
是的
-Are you okay?
-No.
罗谢尔站在浪尖上
Wow, Rochelle Ballard rips!
我已经尽力了 不好意思，罗谢尔，
You wiped out! Sorry, Rochelle.
安妮玛丽在哪里啊？
管她呢？让我来玩一把
-Where's Anne Marie?
-Who cares? Let me play.
嘿，轮到我了
你输了，
Hey, it's my turn.
You got beat.
星期三，一个大浪天
It's hump day.
Wednesday, February 3.
我们已经知道北方和西北方
We've got that high-surf advisory in effect
for the north and northwest-facing shores.
很适合冲浪
There's definitely some size out there
in the water.
听起来有点太熟悉了
Sounds a little bit too familiar.
像是母亲，像是女儿
Like mother, like daughter.
这一直是你的梦想
注定的，
This is your dream.
This is what you were born to do.
不要落后那些家伙
伊登！
-Don't throw it away on this guy.
-Eden!
你不是个儒夫
你只是害怕，
You're not a quitter.
You're just scared.
我要成为世界上最好的冲浪手
I'm gonna be
the best surfer in the world.
总有人脱颖而出的
不是你，就是其他的女孩子
And it's just you and one other girl out there.
It's just you and one other girl out there.
糟了
你在干什么啊？
-Shit!
-What are you doing?
没有干什么
Nothing.
哇，你看起来
什么？
-Wow. You look...
-What?
这件衣服哪儿弄来的？
什么啊？
-Where'd you get that?
-What?
衣服啊
当然是商店里买的了
-The dress.
-From a store.
他买给你的吗？
是的 那又怎么样？
-He bought it?
-Yes, he bought it. So what?
我可以看到你的乳房
太好了
-So, I can see your boobs!
-Great.
她看起来很漂亮
谢谢
-I think she looks beautiful.
-Thank you.
这就是她要的样子
像个巴比娃娃
-She looks the way he wants her to look.
-Like Baywatch Barbie.
潘妮 闭嘴
Penny, shut up.
他要买了的全部吗？
潘妮！我现在没法做这些，喔？
-Is he gonna buy you implants, too?
-Penny! I just can't do this right now, okay?
看，那个小女孩竟然可以做的这么好
Man, that girl could rip.
是谁啊？
你啊
-Who is that?
-You.
那是你第一次在比赛中打败我的时候
That was the first time you beat me
at the Menehune Contest in Haleiwa.
你那时真的很狂
You were such a cocky little shit.
不要总谈些无聊的事情
你怎样成为第一的
Always talking all that trash
and how you would be number one.
我对你很生气
因为我知道你能行的
I was so pissed at you,
'cause I knew you would be.
有天分，还有狗屎运
All talented and shit.
男孩子们在结网 记得吗？
The boys were spinning. Remember that?
他们制定了很多的鸟规则
就是想让你在比赛中出丑
They had to throw up some bullshit rule
barring you from the boys' contest.
我要迟到了
他几天后就走了，晒的一身黑
-I'm gonna be late.
-He's leaving in a few days with a tan.
你呢？你留下了些什么呢？
一双名贵的鞋子吗？
And what are you gonna be left with?
A pair of shoes?
我要白金的
至少是银的
-I wanted platinum, but...
-At least it's an eight.
不是吗？
最好是的
-It is?
-It better be.
他说过是的  一又二分之一个银
He said it was. One and a half.
每个人都觉得我很性感
我是最性感的 你不是
-Everybody thinks I'm sexy.
I'm the sexiest...You ain't sexy!
他什么也不懂的
He don't know anything.
蒂芙尼银饰品
你喜欢蒂芙尼
-Very Tiffany's.
-Then you always get to be at Tiffany's.
他喜欢你的全部，
一夜情
He likes your little some-some.
A little loving one night...
接着你也变了，更有吸引力
-Maybe then, you know.
-And then you get yourself a little upgrade.
晚安 欢迎光临
Good evening, miss.
Welcome to the Lanakai.
吉米，你在开玩笑吧
Jimmy, are you kidding me?
是我，安妮玛丽
哦，真是的，你看起来象变了一个人试的
-It's me. It's Anne Marie.
-Holy shit! You look insane!
谢谢
不用
-Thank you.
-All right.
哇喔，你看起来--
很难看吗
-Wow. You look...
-Weird.
不是，太美了
真的？
-No. No. Gorgeous.
-Really?
走吧  展示一下你自己 喔！
Let's go show you off. Ah!
现在是该那些幸运的人
Okay, now it's time
for a few of you lucky men
学跳我们的草裙舞了
to learn how to do the Tahitian hula.
有人自愿吗？
呵，
-Do we have any volunteers?
-Hell, yeah!
一群聪明伶俐的男人  一群有体型的人
Some intelligent men. Some men of size.
开始，来吧，祝我好运吧
Here I go. All right. Wish me luck.
把你们的手举在空中，
Get those hands up in the air. Come on, now.
快点 来吧，各位怪胎
Come on. Let's go, everybody. Totally freaky!
摇起来吧 快点！
Shake that thing. Come on!
展示一下你自己！摇起来吧！
Shake that thing. Come on! Show them
what you're worth! Shake that thing!
嘿，我是“好热的”海浪预报员，
又一高浪过去了
How's it, wave riders?
We got that high-surf advisory posted again.
现在大概又15-20英尺高
Right now, it's a macking 15-to-20 feet.
明天肯定有浪管
那将是那些勇敢的女孩的好舞台
Out at Pipeline tomorrow,
the girls have the place all to themselves.
我们在这里谈些什么呢？
So, what are we supposed
to talk about with her anyways?
风浪或者彗星
Windex, I guess, or Comet.
这里唯一知道风浪或者彗星的是
The only person who knows
anything about Windex or Comet
卡门，不是我
对啊
-in our house is Carmen, not me.
-You're right.
我希望她不要自认为他会娶她
Right. Seriously, you guys, I hope
she doesn't think he's gonna marry her.
她当然这么认为了
白马王子把她从这里赎了出去
Of course she does. Prince
Charming coming to save her from the toilets.
并且每年有一千万，
And get some of that $10 million a year.
喔，上帝
马特和女侍的经典之作
Oh, God!
Matt and the maid. It's classic.
你们看到她的衣服了吗？
Oh, my God.
Did you guys check out that dress? Hello?
她认为她来到了那里了，班级舞会吗？
God, where does she think
she's going, anyway? The prom?
她的鞋真的很可爱
You guys,
I thought her shoes were totally cute.
相信我，肯定是他给她的，
所有的，都是马特托尔曼给她的
Trust me on this. He made her up.
The whole Matt Tollman makeover.
看那些鞋子，衣服，还有手镯
Did you see the shoes, the dress,
the bracelet?
他的杰作，
His classic line.
哦，上帝
Oh, my God.
你们记得丹尼的女服务员吗？
Do you guys remember
the Denny's waitress?
哦，是的
That's right. I remember.
她原来在丹尼
难怪看起来很眼熟了
She was from Denny's.
I knew she looked familiar.
马特喜欢穷女孩，他就是那样的
Matt loves to slum. That's just how he is.
不要这样说，那是他的个性
Come on. That's his style.
他喜欢那些不值钱的
便宜的野花
-He likes those cheap, little...
-Cheap Barbie...
这双鞋是你的了
Here. They're all yours.
哦上帝
哦上帝 那不就是她吗？
-Oh, my God!
-Oh, my God. Was that just her?
是的
她在这里
-It was.
-She was here.
我们今晚的优胜者
你叫什么名字啊？
Our dancer tonight is Chief...
What's your name?
莱斯利 这里的每个人都叫我“胡桐爸爸“
Leslie, but everybody calls me Poon Daddy!
哇喔，优胜者是“胡桐爸爸“
-Aloha, Chief Poon Daddy!
哦，剑
Oh, yeah!
喔，宝贝，来吧，
Baby, go!
来吧  扭起来吧
Yeah. Shake it for us!
你的“胸”里是不是也有奶啊？
摇起来！摇起来！摇起来！
-You got milk in those coconuts?
Shake it, shake it, shake it!
哦，  哦，
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
安妮玛丽 你去哪里啊？
安妮玛丽 站住
Anne Marie. Where are you going?
Anne Marie? Stop.
怎么 哦，
What the... Oh, man.
喔，安妮玛丽，喔
Ah, Anne Marie, what...
安妮玛丽
Anne Marie.
你到底在干些什么啊？
马特，我也不知道我在干些什么
-What the hell are you doing?
-I don't know, Matt. What am I doing?
前天，我在叫早餐的时候，
The other day,
when I was ordering room service,
服务员称我托尔曼太太，我没有纠正他，
the guy on the phone called me
"Mrs. Tollman," and I didn't correct him,
因为那个时候
我好像真的是了
'cause for a minute,
I liked the way it sounded.
但是我怀疑那个服务员是否真的这么认为
And I was just wondering
if the Denny's waitress felt the same way.
听着
你知道的 我很好，喔
-Listen...
-You know what? I'm fine, okay?
我知道我是谁  我能承受这些
I know what I am, and I'm fine with it.
什么啊，你是谁啊
What? Who are you?
我是你在度假的时候睡过的一个女佣人
我肯定是你故事的主角了
I'm the maid that you slept with on vacation.
I'm the great story you tell
当你告诉别人你是怎样学会冲浪的时候
when someone asks you
how you learned how to surf.
你不相信任何人是吗？
我能吗？我能相信你吗？
-You don't trust anybody, do you?
-Can I? Can I trust you?
干什么？
To do what?
我的意思是-
I mean...
你想要什么？
我想要什么？哦，上帝
-What do you want?
-What do I want? Oh, my God.
我想要
I want
戒烟，去上大学
Penny to quit smoking and to go to college.
我想要
I want...
一次付清电话费，电费和房租等所有的费用
I want to be able to pay the phone
and the electricity and the rent
在一个月里
all in the same month.
我想女孩子能成为冲浪杂志的封面人物，
I want a girl
to be on the cover of Surfmagazine,
如果是我的话更好，如果是其她的女孩子也行的
and that would be great if that girl were me,
but any girl would do. And I want...
我的意思是
我想要妈妈回家
I mean,
I wish my mom would come home.
我真的真的很想赢明天的比赛
And I really, really want
to win Pipe Masters tomorrow.
这就是我想要的
好的，那就实现它啊，
-That's what I want.
-Well, do it.
马特，你不明白的
浪管是世界上最凶的浪
Matt, you don't understand, okay? Pipe...
Pipe is the heaviest wave in the world, okay?
好的，那你就不要在这里工作
你会死的
You don't just get worked there. You die.
有人就死在浪管里
People die there.
如果真发生这种事情 是我没用
一个浪都应付不了
And what happens when I just paddle out
and I don't take off in a single wave?
我不在乎我自己，
'Cause I don't care
if I make a fool out of myself,
但我不想让家人难过
but I do not want to embarrass my family,
我不想让莉娜，伊登和潘妮难过
她们是我的家人
and that's what Lena and Eden
and Penny are. They're my family.
能告诉我该怎么做吗
Just tell me what to do, please.
你想我告诉你该怎么做吗？
是的
-You want me to tell you what to do?
-Yes.
你知道该怎么做的
我不知道，马特，我确实不知道
-You know what to do.
-No, Matt. I honestly don't.
就象那天我在沙滩上碰到的那个女孩
Just be the girl I met on the beach.
谁啊，是谁？
Who? Who was she?
一个从不让其他人告诉她要做什么的女孩
The girl who'd never ask a guy what to do.
早安，各位，欢迎来到比赛现场
Good morning, everybody.
Welcome to the Pipe Masters
瓦胡岛北岸的浪管万岁，
here at Banzai Pipeline,
on the North Shore of Oahu.
今天你将看到女子冲浪最具历史意义的一天
You're gonna be watching
women's surfing history today,
这些女孩们将要征服这些死亡之浪，
as these girls take on
the deadliest waves in the world.
想想尼亚加拉河瀑布直冲而下的情景，
Imagine the Niagara Falls
dumping into two feet of water
这里有熔岩形成硬岩和锋利的珊瑚礁
还有水下洞穴
over hard-rock lava with razor-sharp reef
and underwater caves.
今天可是20英尺的浪啊
It's gonna be a macking 20 feet,
祝福今天参赛的女士们，
so good luck to all the ladies
competing today at the Pipe Masters.
她们都是世界上最好的选手
They may be the best in the world,
命运就在她们自己的手上
but they're gonna have
their hands full today.
今天不仅仅是一次冲浪的比赛，
If you're going down to watch,
it's not a day for a dip in the water.
安妮玛丽 你还好吗？
嗯，
-Anne Marie. You all right?
-Mmm-hmm.
你们走吧
我找个地方停车
You guys get out here.
I'll go find some parking.
太好了，这次的分数肯定很高，
Pretty much
an impossible score at this point.
她远远的落在了后面
但她还是不想放弃
She's way behind, but she's still
gonna try to put it on the line.
她想冲这一次
Looks like she's going for this one.
哦，她的冲浪板被劈成了两半
Oh, and she broke her board.
对冲浪者来说，每天都是刺激的
但是，今日不比往常
You know, any day at Pipeline is critical,
but today,
一次的失误，造成的后果都是惨重的，
one false move,
and the consequences could be disastrous.
在这里丧生的冲浪者远比其他的地方要多
More surfers have died here
than any other spot on the planet combined.
这是第一次让女人来参加这个比赛，
This is the first time the girls
have gotten to compete at Pipeline.
所有的冲浪社团都来了
所有的赞助商，星探
The entire surf media's here today.
Every sponsor, talent scout,
冲浪媒体
都来看这次精心动人的比赛，
the entire surf media,
looking to find the next surf sensation.
哪怕只有一次惊人演出
你都会成为冲浪史上的一页
You get one good ride here today,
and you'll put yourself on the surfing map.
正在冲浪的是琳内特 麦肯齐氏
So out there by herself is Lynette MacKenzie,
在沙滩上的是美耿和被劈坏了的冲浪板
now that Megan's on the beach
with a broken board.
她是个好的冲浪手 她退出了
She's in a nice one. She's coming in.
选择这个浪头肯定是个错误
You really have to commit out here
in order to get the wave.
但我相信她的分数已经很不错了
But I'm sure it'll better the score
she already has...
谢谢你，卡拉
祝你好运，莱恩
-Thanks, Cara.
-Good luck, Layne.
谢谢，我能行的
Thanks. I could use it.
我来参赛的
I'm here for the competition.
你是自愿者吗？
她是参赛者
-Are you a volunteer?
-She's a competitor.
你必须签了这个
Okay, you need to sign this release form.
伤亡保险
"In case of death or dismemberment?"
谢谢
你第四 和凯特斯卡拉特一起
Thank you.
You'll be in heat four with Kate Skarratt.
你可以先到参赛员区等着
You can go ahead and wait
in the competitor's area.
谢谢
祝你好运
-Thank you.
-Good luck.
看起来很吓人啊
Looks scary.
喔，那就是凯特 斯卡拉特
Oh, my gosh. There's Kate Skarratt.
她是个好手
那是罗谢尔 巴拉德
She kills it at Pipe.
And there's Rochelle Ballard.
她是做背切的女王
She's queen of Backdoor.
喔 莱恩比克利
是-我知道她们
-Oh, my gosh. Layne Beachley...
-I know who they are.
什么，我-你行的
我只是想说她们 她们真的很厉害
What? I'm... You're good.
I'm just saying they're, like, really good.
糟了
Shit!
来吧，走
Come on, let's go.
嘿
Hey!
你好
你好，兄弟
What's up?
-What's up, man?
你好，女孩
哪儿可以停车啊，
-What up, girl?
-Where's parking around here?
只要你能找到地方，哪儿都可以的了
Anywhere, I guess. Whatever you can find.
看来这次她要冲了
Looks like she's going on this one.
嘿，安妮玛丽 看我带谁来了
Hey. Hey, Anne Marie. Look what I found.
下一轮 克阿拉 肯内利
Up next, Keala Kennelly.
嗨
Hey.
只是玩玩
你好，冲浪女孩 去做你那鸟事吧
-Just driving by.
-What's up, surfer girl? Do the damn thing!
糟了
Shit!
到20英尺了
太不可思议了 太美妙了
Be alert out there.
It's a super-clean, west-northwest swell.
浪管和浪墙都有了
Pipe and Backdoor are both open.
有点耐心
不要太激动了
Yeah. Just be patient.
Don't get too anxious.
每隔20秒钟就有连续的四浪
注意掌握时间
It's four-wave sets with 20-second intervals.
Take your time.
不要冲第一浪
第三好像事最好的
Don't take the first wave of the set.
Third wave looks the best.
肯内利来了 起飞，俯冲
Here comes Kennelly
taking off. Steep drop.
她做了个底转向
她太凶了
-Takes the bottom turn.
-She's fierce, man.
她被盖住了
She's covered up.
喔，她出来了
She makes it out.
给她鼓掌吧
我怕不一定能成功
Applaud it to her.
I'm way out of my league.
嘿，别想太多了
就当是去娱乐一把
Hey, no worries.
Just go out there and have fun.
“娱乐”
Fun?
下一个 来自澳大利亚的伍伦贡
穿红衣服的凯特 斯卡拉特
Up next from Wollongong,
Australia, we have Kate Skarratt in red.
她的脚底功夫厉害，
这样是她冲浪的时候很有优势
She's a goofy foot,
which favors her at Pipeline.
喜欢挑战大浪
这使她在”绰普“成为了的第一名
Loves charging big waves
and has taken first place at Teahupoo,
一个横冲直撞，大溪地的左撇子
another barreling left-hander in Tahiti.
下一个选手 持外卡参赛
安妮玛丽 查德威克，
Surfing against her, we have wild-card entry
Anne Marie Chadwick,
以前的冠军，后来退出了巡回赛
a formerjunior NSSA champion
who dropped out of the competitive circuit
因为三年前就是在这里的一起事故
after a near-drowning incident
at this very spot just three years ago.
5，4，3，2，1
Five, four, three, two, one.
20分钟一轮，取四轮中最高分
We've got 20-minute heats
today with the top four waves scoring.
选择浪是关键
Wave selection is critical.
如果选错了浪，被卷了进去，
If you pick the wrong wave, wipeout,
get caught inside...
那就是在今天的激烈的比赛中
Well, the currents are fierce today,
你只能在一旁做陪衬了
and you can spend the rest of your heat
just trying to...
怎么样
很好
-How's it going?
-Good.
接近得很漂亮
选择个好浪
Nice set approaching.
We got good sets out the back.
浪得频率真得很好
We have really good consistency
with the swell today.
来了
好像会到15-20英尺
It's on the rise. It's probably gonna get up
to about 15-to-20 feet.
凯特 斯卡拉特来了， 她在滑行，她站起来了
Kate Skarratt's going on this one.
She's paddling. Gets to her feet.
俯冲，来了个漂亮得底转弯
Makes the drop. Solid bottom turn.
看看这个美妙的场景
Look at that pit!
她进入了下一轮，她通过了
She's setting her line.
Breezing to make it out.
尽力到肩部地带
Trying to get in the shoulder.
滑行 喔，最后的一个转弯没有处理好
Traveling, traveling... Oh! She didn't quite
get around that last section.
不管怎样她得分了
She'll get some kind of score for it.
好像是4 1
Looks like it's a 4.1
that came out on the board.
巡逻人员找到了她， 她看起来没有什么事情
Water patrol’s checking on her.
Looks like she's okay.
如果她想继续，她就可以滑回去
She doesn't need a ride.
She's paddling back out.
查德威克 一个人呆在那里
So, Chadwick all alone by herself out there,
yet to even score a ride.
去吧去吧，滑行，好像要来她的第一了
-Go, go! Paddle!
-Headed for her first ride.
停止了
狗屎
-Backs out.
-Shit!
没办法
多漂亮的浪啊
No way.
She's not gonna get any more like that.
真是浪费
她不该停止的，
-What a waste of wave.
-Shoot! She should've gone.
也许刚才会是她的一个好的开始
狗屎
-That would've opened up perfectly.
-Shit!
一个人呆在那里可不行的
你行的
-When you're out there all alone...
-You can do it, girl.
你要相信自己
...you can psych yourself out.
查德威克 在等下一次
你在干什么啊
Chadwick is waiting for the next.
Baby, what are you doing?
凯特 斯卡拉特 选择了一个今天好浪
Kate Skarratt paddling
into one of the best waves of the day.
哦，看看这个浪，像个炸弹一样
Whoa! Look at this wave. It is the bomb.
哦，她滑的过头了
Oh! A little overextended. Goes down.
她被卷下去了
Getting sucked up and over the falls.
希望她没事
Hope she's okay out there.
哦
Ooh!
凯特斯卡拉特退下来了
浪管找到她了
Kate Skarratt down.
Water patrol coming to pick her up.
离开了危险区
Gets her on the sled and out of harm's way.
抓住
Hang on!
哎哟， 各位，请大家不要靠的太近
Okay, everybody. As the Ski comes up
on the beach, please give them some room.
巡逻人员需要些地方，以便他们能做的更好
The water patrol needs some space
to work on Kate Skarratt,
凯特 斯卡拉特最后一次冲浪失败了
who's gone down on that last wave.
他们的冲浪板翻了
主要是这个浪不是很好
They're carrying the backboard down.
This isn't good.
需要乐兰 道医生报告伤势情况
We need Dr. Leland Dao
to report to the medical tent.
乐兰道，请报告帐篷里的情况
请立刻到这里来好吗
Leland Dao, please report to the medical
tent. We need you down here immediately.
来吧来吧
Come on, come on.
冲啊
Charge it!
上，上，上
-Go.
-Go, go, go!
上，上，上
Go! Go!
她站在了板上
哦，落下的很规范
She sets herrail.
Makes the drop. Textbook.
站的太漂亮了
看，多漂亮的浪啊
Oh, it's setting up perfectly.
Look at that beautiful wave.
她能得到一个高分 是的
-She should get a nice score for this one.
-Oh, yes.
足够她进入下一轮的分数
High enough to take her into the next round.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
哦
Oh.
哦，她本来做的很好的
Oh, she got so worked.
我看不到她了，她到哪儿去了
I don't see her. Where is she?
Do you see her?
她还好吗
Man, is she all right?
她在哪里？
浮上来，安妮玛丽，浮上来
-Where is she?
-Come up, Anne Marie. Come up.
哦
Ow.
安妮玛丽遭受了重创
Anne Marie's taking
a heavy beating out there.
抓紧我的手
Grab my hand!
我抓到你了，抓好
I got you. Hang on.
现在她肯定没法管她的分数了， 裁判的分数应该出来了
Not that she probably cares
right now, but the judges' score just came in
最后一次的的分是4．6
and rewarded her a 4.6 for the last ride,
这使她超过了斯卡拉特而进入下一轮
which will move her into the next round
over Skarratt.
安妮玛丽！有事吗？
-Anne Marie.
-Are you okay?
她能好吗？
能好 让我们试一试
-Is she gonna be okay?
-Yes. Just give us a moment.
安妮玛丽！有事吗？
Anne Marie, are you all right?
她还好吧 她还好吧
-Is she gonna be all right?
她没问题的 让她清醒一下
-She'll be okay. Just give her some room here.
她没有问题吧？
应该没有什么问题的
-Is she gonna be okay?
-I think so.
啊
Ah!
我将放些冰块
Gonna put some ice on it.
抬起你的头
Lift your head.
躺着休息会儿
Just lay there and relax for a minute.
嘿
Hey.
如果你再说我是那个沙滩女孩的话，
If you tell me "be the girl on the beach"
right now,
我踢死你
I'm gonna kick your ass.
哦
Oh.
那你怎么样啊 很好
-So how are you feeling?
-I've been better.
Yeah.
我 我的第一次NFL比赛
我在场上找不到位置
My first NFL game,
I got blindsided by Warren Sapp,
告诉你 我一生中重来没有受过那么大的打击
and I'll tell you,
I've never been hit so hard in my life.
我躺在那里，希望哪里受了严重的伤
I just lay there,
praying that something was broken
那样我就没有必要坚持完那场比赛了
so I wouldn't have to get up
and finish the game.
你觉得我是假装吗？
You think I'm faking it right now?
不是的，我知道你撞到了岩石
就象我当初那样
No, I know you got rocked out there,
just like I did.
但是莱斯利让我坐下，
告诉我说那是被撞的最厉害的一次
But Leslie sat me down and said that
that was the hardest I'd ever be hit
他也后悔没有重新回到场上
因此我有回去了
and that I would regret not going back in.
So, I went back in.
你们赢了那场比赛
And you won the game.
没有，实际上我们输了
No, actually, we lost,
我难过死了
and I got my ass kicked.
但那却是我最美好的回忆
But there was this one beautiful pass,
我传了一个绝好的球给奥马尔
one perfect spiral
right into Omar's fingertips,
然后触地得分了
and a touchdown.
光说是没有办法重现当时地情景地
Look, I can't talk you
into going back out there.
太爽了
It seems crazy.
但是我知道你很棒地 我也知道这对你意味着什么
But I know how good you are,
and I know how much this means to you.
我只是不想你到时候后悔你现在做的一切
I just don't want you to spend your life
wondering what could've been.
各位注意了 大浪就要来了
Heads up on the beach, people.
Big set approaching.
嘿 我们必须后退点
Hey, everybody, we have a set out the back.
看好你们的孩子和你们的东西
大浪来了
Watch your kids, watch your belongings.
The water is coming over the berm.
这个很危险
浪到了最高峰了
It's dangerous out there. The water patrol
already has their hands full,
如果你们能稍微的退后一点， 我们将感激不尽
so we'd appreciate it if you'd just back up.
看来今天浪越来越大了
Here, today, we have a rising swell,
因此各位一定要小心了
so I wanted to give a little word of warning
to everybody.
嗨，我知道现在不是时候，我们照张像好吗？
-Guys, look, this is really not a good time.
-Can we get a picture?
什么？ 照张像
-What?
-Can we get a picture?
看啊，在我们这里工作的小妞
See, we're working these chicks over here.
她们说你好像是个有名的 曲棍球运动员或是什么的
They think you're some great hockey player
or something like that.
你开玩笑吧 我真的
-You're kidding.
-No joke, man.
这些我把它照下来
你过这边来，卡拉
I want to get this thing done.
Here you go, Kala.
不好意思，我身上很脏
照了
Sorry, my pits stink,
but that's just the way it goes.
好了，走吧 走右边
Okay, let's go. Right here.
笑一笑  你在度假 看这里
看这里
-Smile. You're on vacation. Over here.
-This way.
笑一笑 来点感情
Fluff your bangs up a little bit.
Just a little bit more attitude in there.
太漂亮了
好的，太好了
-Beautiful.
-All right. Great.
再来一张 来吧
One more, one more. Come on.
嘿 嘿
-Hey.
-Hi.
你确定还要参加吗？ 是的
-You going back out there?
-Yep.
这是个愚蠢的比赛 不值得去冒险
It's just a stupid contest.
Not worth getting hurt over.
我没事的 嘿
-I'll be fine.
-Hey.
什么啊 小心点
-What?
-Be careful.
好的
Yeah.
第二轮开始了
That sounds
the start of the next heat.
查德威克看来要全力一搏了
So, Chadwick's pretty much
got her hands full with this next round.
夏威夷的克阿拉 肯内利现在领先
We have Keala Kennelly from Kauai.
She's a charger.
她可以应付一切大浪， 她可像男人那样的潇洒
She goes on anything.
And she goes like the men out here.
好像滑行一样 她们过去了
There's a bit of a paddle battle
going on out there.
看起来查德威克和肯内利 想滑到最高峰去
Looks like Chadwick and Kennelly
are just paddling for the peak.
查德威克在较里面的位置
Chadwick's got the inside position
as a big set approaches.
大浪来了，她将第一个碰到 上，上
-Looks like she's gonna get the first wave.
-Come on. Come on.
这个滑行赛将决定谁会第一个碰到浪头
This paddle battle is really about
who's gonna get the first wave.
查德威克领现，她好像会碰到第一个
Chadwick in position.
Heading for the first wave.
开始滑行了，她要上了
Starts to paddle. She's going for it.
哦，她被拉回去了 肯内利成功的抓住了机会
Oh, she pulls back.
Kennelly's wide open. She catches the wave.
一次又一次失败
God! Time and time again, man.
她出来了 看她多轻松啊
She's out,
making it look so easy.
但是各位 那可是很难的哦
查德威克开始滑行
But, folks, it's not easy out there.
Chadwick's starting to paddle.
她又来了 还不够好
She paddles for it. Doesn't quite get it.
又浪费了一个好机会
What a waste of wave.
当你考虑到分数的时候，你会很伤心的
That's gotta hurt,
when you know you need a score,
当你得到了一个好的浪，就像这次
and you're going up against
one of the best surfers in this event,
但你却没有上
and you don't go.
有足够的时间让肯内利回到她的位置
Plenty of time being allowed here
for Kennelly to get back in position,
她就在查德威克的旁边滑行，
她好像又要上了
and she's paddled right inside of Chadwick,
and she's looking to catch her next wave.
女士 先生们 克阿拉 肯内利，
Keala Kennelly.
Hands together, ladies and gentlemen.
克阿拉 肯内利，成功了两次了
Keala Kennelly.
A great tube ride out here at the Pipeline.
克阿拉 太棒了
Keala's pretty much got sack.
像男人那样的潇洒
She goes like the men out here.
查德威克好像一次也没有
For some reason,
Chadwick has yet to even ride a wave.
不知怎么一回事情
I don't know what's going on out there.
不知道她是不是在玩心理战
I don't know
if she's just psyching herself out
或者克阿拉根本就不把它放在心上
or if Keala's just putting it to her.
你在干嘛 什么啊？
-What are you doing?
-What?
你是来冲浪还是当浮标的啊
You gonna take a wave,
or are you just gonna sit there like a buoy?
你知道你一次也没有冲，只是坐在那里
Look, you're never gonna catch a wave
sitting all the way over here in the channel.
跟着我，让我带着你
Why don't you follow me over to the peak,
actually get you into one.
给观众一些惊喜
这个浪给你 来吧
Give the crowd something to cheer about.
Let's get you a wave. Come on.
照我说的做，我告诉你什么时候该上
All right, follow me into the line-up,
and I'm gonna tell you to go on a wave.
我说上，你就上
And when I tell you to go, you gotta go.
You gotta paddle your little heart out.
放心大胆的去 不要犹豫 不要后退
不要后退 不要怕，好吗
You can't hesitate. You can't pull back.
You can't hold back. No fear, all right?
因为只要你由于一秒钟，你就玩玩了
Because if you hold back for a second,
you're gonna eat shit.
来吧，跟着我
So, come on. Follow me.
看来下一个浪要来了
It looks like
the next set's approaching.
就是这个，上
Right. This is the one. Go!
滑行，滑行 上  滑行，滑行
Paddle, paddle! Go, girl! Paddle! Paddle!
Go! Paddle!
继续
Go!
啊
Yeah!
上
Whoo! Go!
哦，我的天
Oh, my God!
你没事吧
没事，没事
-You all right?
-I'm okay. I'm okay!
真的没事
是的，没事
-You sure?
-Yeah, I'm okay.
回去吧
Get back out there, then.
只有两分钟了
With only two minutes left in her heat,
查德威克 努力的回到了她的位置，
Chadwick struggles to get back
into the line-up
因此她可以开始
so she can catch this one wave.
查德威克 还没有一次有效的冲浪，她还没有得分
Chadwick yet to even score a good ride,
a scoring ride.
她要为她挽回点面子 克阿拉完全的控制了比赛
She needs to redeem herself here.
Keala is absolutely dominating this heat,
查德威克需要给她的记分牌上留下个分数
and Chadwick needs to collect a scoring ride
on this one.
哦 你好吗
Ouch. You all right?
那个太差了，我要下一个
-That was nasty.
-It's okay. I want another one.
你要下一个
是
-You want another one?
-Yep.
就是那个
来吧，这是最后的一个了 来吧
That's the spirit!
Shake off that last wave and let's do this.
只有20秒钟了，正让人激动
-Less than 20 seconds remaining...
-Feel that adrenaline in you? Use it.
安妮玛丽 查德威克只有一次机会了
...Anne Marie Chadwick only has
one more chance.
用力划，女孩
Paddle, girl.
看，那是一天中最好的一个浪
On the outside, here comes one of
the best sets of the whole day coming in.
太美妙了
We have lines stacked to the horizon.
来了
Here comes the set.
就是这个
好的，来吧！ 上，上
This is the one. This is the one, right here.
All right. Come on. Go! Come on. Go! Go!
上，女孩
查德威克就在那里，在使劲的滑行
Come on, girl. Go!
Chadwick is there. Paddle hard!
用力划！用力划！
上！上！
-Paddle hard! Paddle hard!
-Go! Go!
上，上，上
这是你的，不要迟疑
-Go! Go! Go!
Yeah. This is yours! Don't pull back!
上，上，上 上，上，上
-Go! Go!
-Go! Go! Go!
哦
Whoo!
哦，狗屎
Oh, shit
Yeah!
哦
Whoo!
Yeah!
哦
Whoo!
她成功了
她是我们这里的人
-She makes it!
-That's my bitch!
太棒了
That was insane!
哦
Whoo!
看裁判给分了
他们已经有了结果了 好像一致通过了
Waiting on the judges' scores.
They're coming in.
看看记分牌，好像是10分
Looks like unanimous 10s across the board.
不是很高，但是超过了肯内利，进入了下一轮
Not enough to overtake Kennelly
and move into the next round,
但是她是今天的英雄
but she is a hero with the crowd here today.
哦，她是我的姐姐
That's my sister! Whoo!
她是我的姐姐
That's my sister!
难以用言语来表示
Just words don't explain it.
因为 安妮玛丽 查德威克 做了一次如此成功的表演
For Anne Marie Chadwick
to get a ride like that
所有北岸的冲浪社团都看在眼里
with the entire North Shore
surf community watching...
太棒了
-That was insane!
-Yeah!
我们这为她骄傲
I'm so proud of her.
可以签个名吗 可以签个名吗
-Can I have your autograph?
-That was insane.
那些都是我教她的
She's my bitch.
I taught her everything she knows.
你叫什么名字
她是我们这里的女孩
-What's your name?
-That's right. That's our girl.
嘿
Hey.
真让人敬佩
谢谢
-That was awesome.
-Thank you.
嘿，你该看看冲浪板，伊登的冲浪板
Hey, you should check out the boards.
嗨，安妮玛丽， 借过 嗨
-Hey, Anne Marie.
-Hi.
我是“绿洲”的杰西卡
Excuse me, Anne Marie.
I'm Jessica from Billabong.
能和你谈谈关于加入我们社团的事情吗
I'd love to talk to you
about being on our team.
排队等等吧，宝贝 喔
-Wait your turn, honey.
-Okay.
她知道她和上镜吗
-Does she know she got beat?
-Nice, isn't it?
嘿
Hey.
哦
Oh.
你干成了你的鸟事
谢谢
-You did the damn thing, girl.
-Thanks.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 你太让人不可思议了
哦，感觉怎么样了？
You were so amazing.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
哦，太棒了
-Yes.
-Oh, that was insane.
但是我要提醒你的是，我们的冲浪课还没有结束
But I still think you owe me
a few surf lessons.
哦，是的
是的
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
想去那里吗
You want to go out there?
只要你能温柔一点
Only if you're gentle.
不仅仅是-
Not a chance.